[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: None

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OL,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,95,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,1
Style: 宣传信息,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.2,0.2,9,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,70,100,6,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 二维码,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 声明,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HC85A5A5A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 音乐,方正兰亭特黑简体,20,&H000EDDE5,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组1,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,134
Style: Bosch片头,经典综艺体简,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HE6E28609,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Bosch歌词,方正字迹-杜慧田硬笔楷书,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HDC0B9016,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Bosch职员,经典综艺体简,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: BoschS3E10特效,苹方 中等,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.41,0:00:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用工作吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.70,0:00:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要啊 我在一艘私人运营的船上打杂
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.99,0:00:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去了香港 西班牙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.80,0:00:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布宜诺斯艾利斯 基本老板说哪就去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.84,0:00:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,婊子养的糜烂货
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.47,0:00:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们唤醒了某些东西 有些人不想让我们
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.36,0:00:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道迈克尔的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.44,0:00:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个什么波塞冬到底是谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.97,0:00:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个变态
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.34,0:00:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中情局里一个失意的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.11,0:00:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,政策研究员 在中情局内部创立了一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.21,0:00:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫"21空洞"的组织
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.31,0:00:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.85,0:00:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮助被关押在世界各地
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.08,0:00:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的囚犯越狱
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.85,0:00:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯勒曼遇害之前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.15,0:00:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在调查21空洞的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.89,0:00:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你调查系统内部
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.16,0:00:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,存在内鬼的可能性
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.56,0:00:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没想到你会在这时候打电话给我
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.29,0:00:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得尽快见面
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.59,0:00:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在找那个叔叔去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.40,0:00:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么叔叔 宝贝儿?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.46,0:00:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我这个的叔叔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.73,0:00:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.90,0:00:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底遇到什么麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.17,0:00:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我们你要去哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.74,0:00:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿过沙漠三百英里外的费阿刻斯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.21,0:00:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个自治区 没有ISIL
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.17,0:00:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以带你们过去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.38,0:00:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,费阿刻斯 我们找到了!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.26,0:01:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在城里的时候 我就告诉过你 你会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.99,0:01:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.06,0:01:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对我下了毒
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.65,0:01:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你画画越来越好 真是不可思议 迈克
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的 这...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.93,0:01:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好看了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.86,0:01:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个希腊英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.26,0:01:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好像受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.90,0:01:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们早晚都会受伤的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.34,0:01:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是古希腊英雄的伟大之处
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.20,0:01:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是真实的 而不是超人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.31,0:02:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们也会受伤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.24,0:02:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也会死
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思 哥们儿 最后一点儿就好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.06,0:02:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得把伤口洗干净 知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去好多了 不是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.76,0:02:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没问题的 坚持住 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.56,0:02:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.83,0:02:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有进展了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们那边的那位朋友有艘船
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.26,0:02:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他正要往希腊运趟走私货
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.44,0:02:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他能带你弟弟去第一世界看医生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.41,0:02:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一世界的人都认为他是肯尼尔·奥提斯
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.61,0:02:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一见面他们就会逮捕他的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.14,0:02:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.61,0:02:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能怎么办 看着他死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.95,0:02:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底算是个什么哥哥啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.88,0:02:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再说一次这种话
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.18,0:02:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发誓一定亲手杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.56,0:02:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许还有第三个选择
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.37,0:03:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一天回去上班感觉如何
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.17,0:03:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须承认 我从来没这么有成就感过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.64,0:03:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,往一帮十八岁小屁孩的头脑里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.88,0:03:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灌输博弈论
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.31,0:03:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管他们只是忙着互发色情短信
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.48,0:03:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.92,0:03:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正常的日子离我们不远了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.52,0:03:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这必须庆祝一下
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.76,0:03:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,值得庆祝
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.79,0:03:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧 咱们到外面坐坐
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.16,0:03:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一会就过去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.17,0:03:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.47,0:03:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们找到迈克尔了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.67,0:03:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还是我们的那个迈克尔吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.17,0:03:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 莎拉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.76,0:03:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 莎拉 他中毒了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.70,0:03:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们觉得是防冻剂中毒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.93,0:03:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他失血过多
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.20,0:03:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要补血
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.54,0:03:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.97,0:03:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是防冻剂的话 他还需要很多东西
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.57,0:03:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.84,0:03:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要去希腊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.54,0:03:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么方法能在黑市获得医疗救助么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.78,0:04:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不不不不  这事儿你们没法
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.41,0:04:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在黑市干
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.98,0:04:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 林肯 他需要输血
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.18,0:04:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔是B型阴性血 懂么?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.92,0:04:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概只有百分之一的人是这种血型
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.96,0:04:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去那儿是找不到这种血型的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.72,0:04:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也熬不到你找着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.96,0:04:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非这种血型自己来找你
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.13,0:04:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我稍后给你回电
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.20,0:04:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.44,0:04:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.04,0:04:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.94,0:04:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得走了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.88,0:04:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.31,0:04:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去克里特岛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.85,0:04:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.28,0:04:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们找到他了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.92,0:04:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.35,0:04:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他中毒了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.59,0:04:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔? 你的前夫 迈克尔?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.99,0:04:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.32,0:04:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等 等一下
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.49,0:04:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真的还活着?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.89,0:04:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他刚刚联系你了?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.43,0:04:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 他需要帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.90,0:04:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我是唯一一个能帮助他的人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.58,0:05:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐飞机比他们坐船去更快
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.81,0:05:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂 莎拉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.44,0:05:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不欠他的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.31,0:05:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道自己将面对什么 太不安全了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.28,0:05:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会没事的 我别无选择
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.68,0:05:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.02,0:05:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地狱般的一周
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.22,0:05:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 我知道你有无数个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.16,0:05:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.02,0:05:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法看着我儿子的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.56,0:05:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他 我明明可以救他父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.66,0:05:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却眼睁睁看他死了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.00,0:05:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从没见过他亲生父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.37,0:05:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.97,0:05:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那如果我让你不要去呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.47,0:05:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"如果"是个太沉重的词
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.14,0:05:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅各布 你是在叫我别去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.61,0:05:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.18,0:05:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 当然不是
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.18,0:05:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.26,0:06:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不该把她牵扯进来的 林肯
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.83,0:06:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴 你就要见到
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.40,0:06:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你七年没见的老婆了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.97,0:06:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 我扶你 我扶你 - 你解开缆绳了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.91,0:06:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.74,0:06:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.65,0:06:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不记得自己被关了多久了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.45,0:06:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在进奥杰吉厄监狱之前 我只有一套公寓 一个脑袋
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.42,0:06:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和一部手机
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.49,0:06:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墙壁将我包围
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.02,0:06:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,使我看不见外面的世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.86,0:06:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这里
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.40,0:06:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有墙壁
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.83,0:06:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很久没这么自由了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.40,0:06:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以重新开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.11,0:06:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你说你需要我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.11,0:06:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然我更想留下来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.08,0:06:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贾 你是个自由的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.61,0:06:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选择权在你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.72,0:06:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我欠你一条命
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.62,0:06:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带我回到了这个世界
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.12,0:06:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他早日康复 你们一路平安
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.96,0:07:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯 我会的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.03,0:07:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.40,0:07:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 嘿 嘿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.63,0:07:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得问个明白
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.10,0:07:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的拥有佛莱迪·摩克瑞的骨灰?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.54,0:07:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基思·理查兹真的吸了他亡父的骨灰?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.31,0:07:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.91,0:07:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.15,0:07:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好活着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.95,0:07:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也是 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.33,0:07:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林肯
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有多久到希腊?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.60,0:07:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十二小时
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.67,0:07:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莎拉十二个小时内就会到
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.27,0:07:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我没有十二个小时可活了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.46,0:09:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前是对的 我们有麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.94,0:09:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很显然 我们昨天去国安局之后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.04,0:09:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,国务院就开始问21空洞的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.41,0:09:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们没有任何可靠证据
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.41,0:09:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,21空洞根本就不存在
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.48,0:09:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波塞冬会做好内部整顿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.92,0:09:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦不会就此消失
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.09,0:09:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个国务院的特工想在我们降落之后
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.32,0:09:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上跟我们见面
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.47,0:09:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦去哈尼亚
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.77,0:09:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.49,0:09:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里很安全
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.29,0:09:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来这里的时候才用这个房子
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.86,0:10:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能给他弄点吃的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.49,0:10:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来 吃的在船上
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.69,0:10:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.30,0:10:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他鼓鼓劲
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.03,0:10:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.97,0:10:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噢 天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.91,0:10:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄 你一定得撑住 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.45,0:10:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有很多事没有告诉我呢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.46,0:10:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得告诉我为什么我是你的执鞭之手
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.39,0:10:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.73,0:10:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你经历了这么多
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.31,0:10:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在可不能在我面前死掉啊 迈克尔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.51,0:10:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫了你迈克尔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.31,0:10:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我第一... 第一次知道你的真名
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.98,0:11:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我觉得...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.39,0:11:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自打相遇我们就像亲兄弟 你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.90,0:11:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而现在 林肯在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.90,0:11:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我第一次觉得自己是个外人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.94,0:11:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.14,0:11:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我失去了...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.98,0:11:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的亲人一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.85,0:11:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以迈克尔 你不能死
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.12,0:11:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.41,0:12:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林肯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.34,0:13:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好想你
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.88,0:13:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你治好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.65,0:13:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们再说话 好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.12,0:13:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你治好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.63,0:13:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.56,0:13:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动 没事的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.03,0:13:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林肯
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.07,0:13:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能帮我把那个衣架拿过来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.04,0:13:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能给我拿张椅子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.84,0:13:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.20,0:14:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给他输血
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.70,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是阴性O型血
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.94,0:14:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是万能血
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.54,0:14:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是他唯一能接受的血型
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.04,0:14:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这就是命运 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.18,0:14:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会活下去吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.22,0:14:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.92,0:14:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会活下去的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.23,0:14:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他几小时
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.86,0:14:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很坚强
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.50,0:14:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们... 我们让你俩单独待会
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.84,0:14:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.77,0:14:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.98,0:14:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在你身边
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.75,0:14:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得想办法离开这个岛
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.96,0:15:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.63,0:15:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说你...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.30,0:15:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我错了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.37,0:15:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何人能有个像你这样的哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.84,0:15:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是三生有幸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.78,0:15:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这样的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.51,0:15:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.65,0:15:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是运气使然
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.75,0:15:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我们共患难
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.49,0:15:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在已经是我们的家人了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.86,0:15:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得为此喝一杯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.26,0:15:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.07,0:15:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐飞机真的是不可能了?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.70,0:15:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.87,0:15:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机场比医院还行不通
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.81,0:15:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且肯尼尔·奥提斯这个名字招人耳目
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.84,0:15:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们看见他就会立马杀了他的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.18,0:15:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再找一艘船?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.55,0:16:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,横渡大西洋?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.58,0:16:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽不是个水手 却也知道这港口没船能
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.82,0:16:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走那么远
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.33,0:16:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要一艘大船
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.50,0:16:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一艘不介意装放射性货物的船
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.31,0:16:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好 我想跟进我们上次的谈话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.05,0:16:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显中情局和国务院
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.79,0:16:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直在共享关于肯尼尔·奥提斯的信息
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.82,0:16:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要问你们的是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.06,0:16:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥提斯杀了阿布·阿米尔
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.76,0:16:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为这个国家做了贡献
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.16,0:16:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么你们昨天在国安局还
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.80,0:16:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想把他杀了?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.83,0:16:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先走出停机坪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.87,0:16:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们会告诉你我们的调查研究
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.54,0:16:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这完全是官僚主义的沟通不畅
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.27,0:16:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以解决
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.51,0:17:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你们 我们和中情局联系过了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.88,0:17:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中情局并没有批准你们昨天造访国安局
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.18,0:17:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至没人知道你们去了那里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.98,0:17:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你们到底在为谁效力?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.52,0:17:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么想把肯尼尔·奥提斯干掉?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.63,0:17:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没想到我会在见到你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.13,0:17:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本不应该见到我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.20,0:17:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.91,0:17:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会告诉你你想知道的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.38,0:17:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但首先 我需要你给我一样东西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.91,0:17:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都可以
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.38,0:17:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我一张我儿子的照片
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.46,0:17:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们昨天没有去国安局
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.33,0:17:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说 你们搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.56,0:17:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我说谎才是搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.20,0:17:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以起诉你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.96,0:17:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在国安局有熟人 她给了我证据
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.90,0:18:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有给他起名叫小迈克尔吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.67,0:18:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你我保证 我肯定不会这样叫他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.04,0:18:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是第一个很好的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.61,0:18:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你一个模子刻出来的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.19,0:18:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.10,0:18:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.28,0:18:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.55,0:18:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅各布?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.65,0:18:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅各布
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.19,0:18:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雅各布就是波塞冬
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.40,0:19:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道 我没疯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.63,0:19:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现他撒谎了 但是他...他...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.14,0:19:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天哪 他掩饰得太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.77,0:19:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他..人一直很诚实而且当时还受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.81,0:19:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就相信了他说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.44,0:19:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是谁?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.88,0:19:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.65,0:19:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是中情局特工 是个卧底
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.12,0:19:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在主管运行这个叫“21空洞”的组织
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.38,0:19:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这跟你有什么关系?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.75,0:19:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他看上了我的本事
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.49,0:19:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勒索我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.06,0:19:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说如果我不同意为他工作
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.53,0:19:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会来追捕你和林肯
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.33,0:19:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你们俩都送进监狱
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.25,0:19:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他证明给我看了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.39,0:19:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说我将再也见不到你们俩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.73,0:19:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包括迈克
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.62,0:19:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逼我伪造了我的死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.66,0:19:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他利用了我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.30,0:19:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他娶了我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.83,0:19:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我知道他是你丈夫 我发誓...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.67,0:19:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 不 不 不 不
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.77,0:19:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不怪你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.80,0:20:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我..
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.64,0:20:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是现在? 你为什么要现在回来?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.01,0:20:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那张折纸...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.88,0:20:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,4年前 他背叛了我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.65,0:20:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我知道为什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.28,0:20:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想让我退出
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.79,0:20:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他就能得到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.49,0:20:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么背叛的你?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.89,0:20:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他安排了一次会议
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.16,0:20:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们本来应该讨论我的下一个任务
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.06,0:20:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他没有告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.70,0:20:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要见一个叫哈兰·盖恩斯的人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.17,0:20:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中情局的副局长
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.07,0:20:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,盖恩斯当时正在调查21空洞
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.27,0:20:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找这背后的叛徒
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.58,0:20:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个时候我意识到我干的事没有被中情局批准过
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,波塞冬那天晚上开枪杀了盖恩斯
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.95,0:20:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阻止他调查
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.56,0:20:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让我把尸体拖走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.96,0:20:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伪装成什么都没有发生过的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.39,0:20:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看过关于这件事的照片 他们太可恶
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.66,0:21:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他选了正好拍到我拖动盖恩斯尸体的那断录像
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.40,0:21:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,删除了对他不利的片段
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.57,0:21:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我被陷害了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.64,0:21:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他当时对我控制得越来越死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.57,0:21:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我什么也做不了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.94,0:21:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少 他是这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.91,0:21:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我知道波塞冬不按指示行事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.72,0:21:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且活动于中情局工作范围之外
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.18,0:21:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始计划回到你身边的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.62,0:21:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你没回来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.99,0:21:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别的人替代了你...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.99,0:21:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的脸 你的过去 你全部的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.86,0:21:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨拉 这是计划中的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.63,0:21:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了保护我们的家庭
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.50,0:21:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔 他现在跟我们的儿子在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.30,0:21:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跟迈克在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.57,0:21:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.18,0:21:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诺亚 你能给我们建艘船吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.08,0:21:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 我能搞个更好的过来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.82,0:21:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给谁打电话呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.52,0:22:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个真的有船的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.20,0:22:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.70,0:22:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苏克雷 是我
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.90,0:22:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林肯? 我以为你会在中东
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.94,0:22:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回不来了呢 哥们儿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.21,0:22:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔在哪? 你找到他了吗？
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.11,0:22:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 这就是我打电话来的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.18,0:22:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在克里特岛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.85,0:22:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要悄悄偷渡回美国
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.78,0:22:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.45,0:22:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们之间隔了大半个地球 哥们
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.25,0:22:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚在摩洛哥卸完货
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.92,0:22:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在说什么? 摩洛哥跟克里特离得很近啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.42,0:22:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 我知道 当然是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.29,0:22:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的意思是这不是我的船
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.53,0:22:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  现在这个船把捎带我们回去要多少钱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.36,0:22:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没法捎带你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.07,0:22:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们必须租下整艘船
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.80,0:22:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老板要价5万 林肯
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.24,0:22:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们想要回美国 5万
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.47,0:22:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,5万?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.71,0:22:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是想回国而已
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.01,0:22:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我们没有那么多钱
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.65,0:22:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在有了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.31,0:23:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个 这是我祖母给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.85,0:23:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个传家宝肯定值那么多钱了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.49,0:23:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是它最大的用处了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.69,0:23:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.49,0:23:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有钱了 苏克雷 来克里特
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.57,0:23:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他怀疑你可能发现他的真实身份之前
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.82,0:23:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会伤害迈克的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.54,0:23:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你揭穿他的真实面目
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.01,0:23:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可能就会出手了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.67,0:23:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比我更了解他
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.44,0:23:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键是 没人了解他
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.21,0:23:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以 我该怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.01,0:23:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟他玩下去 你装成什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.65,0:23:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦发现有机会能带着迈克逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.69,0:23:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶快跑 消失
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.32,0:23:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会尽快赶回美国
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.52,0:23:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到你
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.23,0:23:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来好多了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.00,0:23:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脸色还是有点差 但是好多了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.83,0:23:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有你这个出色的医生在身边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.67,0:24:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会伪装好
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.64,0:24:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会跟他玩下去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.18,0:24:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果他伤害我们的儿子我就杀了他
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.75,0:24:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.44,0:24:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要回到我们身边
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.69,0:24:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一个人离开克里特岛了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.69,0:24:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留下了迈克尔 说明迈克尔肯定会在接下来的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.93,0:24:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一两天之内回到美国
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.70,0:24:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁打的电话? -他要么坐船要么坐飞机 
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.69,0:25:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以把他的样貌给所有的港口 海关报备
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.95,0:25:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在接下来的48小时
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.64,0:25:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点注意从克里特岛来的船
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.71,0:25:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定在其中一艘上
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.48,0:25:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 不能让他入境 - 雅各布?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.85,0:25:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在跟妈妈打电话吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.18,0:25:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 你妈妈快回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.55,0:25:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克·斯科菲尔德
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.89,0:25:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟 你比别人多了好几条命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.79,0:25:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得快要用光了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.29,0:25:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真他妈的死而复生了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.93,0:25:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.56,0:25:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快给我说说
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.13,0:25:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死后发生的所有的的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.87,0:25:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟 你又活了?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.67,0:25:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机长贪得无厌是个狗娘养的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.21,0:25:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别和他打交道 他手里有枪
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.81,0:25:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 还有各种走私的货物 - 船长
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.05,0:26:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我说起过的货物
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.88,0:26:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,付钱
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.75,0:26:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要的五万块呢?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.95,0:26:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这儿
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.72,0:26:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过要现金的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.62,0:26:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是蓝宝石 六克拉
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.96,0:26:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无缝宝石 四周是二点五克拉的钻石斜面
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.60,0:26:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,市价是十二万五千
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.53,0:26:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以半价抵押还有盈余
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.21,0:26:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是个假的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.41,0:26:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把那你扔海里
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.42,0:26:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到船上找你是最后的希望了 朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.39,0:26:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你不喜欢水
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.99,0:26:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是 你记得没错 不过我有犯罪记录
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.26,0:26:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么人愿意冒险雇我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.93,0:26:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有 这艘船给了我机会
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.36,0:26:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞些副业...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.10,0:26:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是我到这艘船上的真正原因
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.07,0:26:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这宝贝...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.04,0:26:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承载在我的所有积蓄
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.20,0:26:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你们说 这是个巨大的生意
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.57,0:27:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我几个月前把这些带上来的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.28,0:27:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算你们幸运 让你们见识下
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.55,0:27:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的姑娘们
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.48,0:27:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.82,0:27:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么 性爱娃娃?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.85,0:27:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,错 有点档次好吗 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.09,0:27:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准确的说法是充气娃娃 高品质的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.89,0:27:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很贵的 超仿真
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.69,0:27:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.68,0:27:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.92,0:27:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 你好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.00,0:28:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克在哪儿?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.30,0:28:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡着了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.70,0:28:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小朋友今天玩得很嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.37,0:28:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是 最要紧的是
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.58,0:28:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔怎么样了?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.11,0:28:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能帮到他吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.21,0:28:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到那儿的时候他差不多已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.75,0:28:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他 那时一直在昏睡
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.42,0:28:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我... 我尽我所能挽救他 ...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.36,0:28:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让他状况稳定了下来 但是他变了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.33,0:28:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他 ... 他变得不是昔日我认识的那个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.63,0:28:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们把我送到了机场 就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.57,0:28:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.67,0:28:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,林肯和其他人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.08,0:28:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.78,0:28:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克在哪儿?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.35,0:28:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 你说他睡了 - 是睡了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.19,0:28:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在朋友家过夜
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.72,0:28:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好 哪个朋友?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.59,0:28:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在帕特里克家里
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.53,0:29:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你祖母的戒指哪儿去了?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.77,0:29:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是个笨蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.20,0:29:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在去的路上为了安全把它摘下来
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.10,0:29:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想它被偷走
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.07,0:29:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我回来的路上再想找它就不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.68,0:29:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在飞机场喊了出来差点被人从飞机上扔出来
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.34,0:29:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.81,0:29:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和我们在五角大楼的人谈过了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.38,0:29:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一份海军警报刚刚发出
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.98,0:29:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯尼尔·奥提斯被发现
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.12,0:30:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地中海的一艘货轮上
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.72,0:30:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那艘船的船长报告的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.69,0:30:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海军会采取什么行动?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.36,0:30:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近的支援登陆艇战斗船
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.46,0:30:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在移动介入
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.30,0:30:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海豹突击队已部署
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.86,0:30:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们的命令是?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.47,0:30:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搜寻并摧毁肯尼尔·奥提斯
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.90,0:30:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.34,0:30:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的任务是放出消息
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.11,0:30:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来留给海豹突击队完成他们的任务
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.21,0:30:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.15,0:30:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是经历了炼狱啊 朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.52,0:30:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要有信心 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.29,0:30:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.32,0:30:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么样 林肯
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.76,0:30:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为林肯有了一个秘密女友
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.79,0:30:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导航员姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.80,0:30:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是我的女友
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.16,0:30:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许苏克雷会给你介绍个性爱娃娃
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.73,0:30:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不是娃娃 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.07,0:30:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 抱歉 是充气娃娃
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.60,0:30:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说 换个话题吧 拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.30,0:30:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道的 应该要说点能解决问题的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.07,0:30:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错 嗯... 这副牌可不会给我们答案
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.88,0:31:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从外面锁住了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.92,0:31:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们出卖你了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.99,0:31:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是被通缉的恐怖分子
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.99,0:31:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他刚刚说的你他妈的都听到哪儿去了?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.22,0:31:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为就是打个比方
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.19,0:31:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 看在上帝的份上
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.46,0:31:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有其他办法
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.89,0:31:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从船舱里出去
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.83,0:31:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有船员都到顶层甲板上来 手举起来
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.57,0:31:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照做否则我们将会开枪射击
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.04,0:31:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这艘船现在被美国海军控制
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.91,0:31:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好我们将要登船
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.81,0:31:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有伴儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.48,0:31:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说咱们跳下去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.75,0:31:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下去还有很远呢
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.92,0:31:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唯一的通路
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.13,0:31:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太远了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.98,0:31:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个想法...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.32,0:31:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...可是会挺痛的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.40,0:32:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈啰?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.34,0:32:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海瑟 是我 听好 我不能多说
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.17,0:32:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我想让你现在就去接走迈克 可以吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.38,0:32:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道帕特里克·门罗住哪里吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.84,0:32:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.84,0:32:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.05,0:32:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着 我迟点会解释的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.58,0:32:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要带他回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.45,0:32:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他跟着你 我一搞定就会过来
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.58,0:32:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以帮我做到吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.92,0:32:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呃 好 我现在就去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.19,0:32:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都还好吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.56,0:32:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.03,0:32:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出发
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.84,0:32:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,六点钟方向 其他的跟我走
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.04,0:32:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.45,0:32:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一 二 三 四
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.69,0:32:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走 走
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.70,0:33:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走左边 你右边
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.34,0:33:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从窗口逃走了!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.41,0:33:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从窗口逃走了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.71,0:33:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到什么?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.01,0:33:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不到他们
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.81,0:33:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔法一号 阿尔法二号立刻去左舷
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.88,0:33:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.32,0:33:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.72,0:33:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松...给我松绑!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.43,0:33:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么名字?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.46,0:33:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,费尔南多
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.30,0:33:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,费尔南多·苏克雷
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.90,0:33:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一名船员 你可以看下班表
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.03,0:33:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和这事一点关系都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.87,0:33:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在班表上找一下费尔南多·苏克雷
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.21,0:33:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疑犯是在班表上
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.93,0:33:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带他去驾驶室
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.41,0:33:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 警官
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.08,0:33:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.49,0:34:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能有任何人离开这艘船 明白吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.95,0:34:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的 警官
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.94,0:34:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不认识什么肯尼尔·奥提斯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.67,0:34:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙叫斯科菲尔德
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.94,0:34:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好多年没见过他了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.21,0:34:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打给我 他说他要搭船
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.24,0:34:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在引擎舱进行追捕
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.21,0:34:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着他
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.38,0:34:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人是叫斯科菲尔德!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.52,0:34:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苏克雷说的那扇门
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.16,0:34:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在那!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.56,0:34:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动! 别动!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.76,0:34:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.70,0:34:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们包围他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.73,0:34:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大伙 快! 快点!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.53,0:34:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.64,0:34:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡住了!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.80,0:34:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 快点! - 门卡住了!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.24,0:34:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡住了!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.34,0:34:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,熏他们出来 去!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.09,0:35:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,催泪弹
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.62,0:35:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会进入通风系统 会毁了我的船的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.16,0:35:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是个失败的人 苏克雷
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.30,0:35:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我雇过最糟的船员
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.63,0:35:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把这趟破事带到我的船上
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.30,0:35:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是你的朋友 他们要去哪里?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.14,0:35:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是朋友的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.27,0:35:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好多年没见过他们了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.17,0:35:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这让我想到了些事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.51,0:35:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如你告诉这些友好的海豹队员
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.04,0:35:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎样收下他们的好处 让他们上船的?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.15,0:35:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能他们是你的朋友 不是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.82,0:35:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了 好了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.02,0:35:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听他们提到了十七号货仓
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.50,0:35:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十七号货仓
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.87,0:35:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那个超级秘密的货仓是吧?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.74,0:36:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器和弹药?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.24,0:36:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文森特 船队可能也有武装
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.48,0:36:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们找到那些东西的话应该就不会喜欢你了吧 老兄
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.41,0:36:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文森特
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.11,0:36:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能也会被列到恐怖分子怀疑名单上
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.75,0:36:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,文森特 收到吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.75,0:36:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听不清
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.69,0:36:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没用的墨西哥佬 你都计划好的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.56,0:36:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留在这
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.57,0:36:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十七号还封着
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.41,0:36:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,船长?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.81,0:36:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可是波多黎各人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.35,0:36:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12点钟方向 你听到了吗?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.86,0:36:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.75,0:37:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快 快 快走
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.68,0:37:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.02,0:37:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这条船正在改变航向
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.20,0:37:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做到了 兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.86,0:37:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在回不了头了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.71,0:37:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看他们下一步要干什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.42,0:37:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还记得我们的蜜月吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.93,0:37:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得 当然了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.77,0:37:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我敞开心扉
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.73,0:37:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我你为在狐狸河监狱的作为感到羞愧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.51,0:37:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我你有时希望自己
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.78,0:37:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从没听过迈克尔·斯科菲尔德这个名字
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.91,0:37:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至承认你说谎了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.25,0:37:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前把一切都瞒着我
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.42,0:38:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还告诉我你最终如何清白脱身
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.58,0:38:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把一切抛之脑后
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.49,0:38:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.29,0:38:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原谅了你的谎言
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.46,0:38:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的过去
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.63,0:38:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接受了你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.37,0:38:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱你 也爱迈克
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.50,0:38:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道这对你来说还不够吗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.55,0:38:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.82,0:38:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.99,0:38:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接到他了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.66,0:38:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.33,0:38:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.93,0:38:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正往我家走呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.50,0:38:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨 妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.73,0:38:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 海瑟 太谢谢你了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.47,0:38:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上就到
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.58,0:39:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导航仪被毁了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.04,0:39:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制器也坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.21,0:39:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.51,0:39:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,货船偏离航向了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.15,0:39:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在向阿尔及利亚水域全速航行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.08,0:39:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能修好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.52,0:39:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要花时间
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.59,0:39:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估计到时候
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.80,0:39:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就出了公海了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.39,0:39:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猎鹰一号请求指令
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.46,0:39:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出了状况
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.20,0:40:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.66,0:40:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海豹突击队没能拿下奥提斯
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.93,0:40:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知为何船的控制仪被毁了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.34,0:40:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在正往阿尔及利亚水域前行
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.68,0:40:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的士兵还在船上
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.37,0:40:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果他们接着在船上狙杀他们
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.94,0:40:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会引起外交事故了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.28,0:40:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海军那边刚刚打电话暂停了行动
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.74,0:40:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧 好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.35,0:40:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海豹突击队完成不了 我们就升级行动
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.25,0:40:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不该带把刀去参加枪战
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.18,0:40:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来我来处理 谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.77,0:40:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长官
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.90,0:40:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请讲
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.40,0:40:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有一个请求 一个紧急请求
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.34,0:40:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你会发现我们的利益是一致的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.86,0:41:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.29,0:41:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.29,0:41:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.63,0:41:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.79,0:41:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦 天啊 不 不 不 不!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.32,0:41:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿 你会需要这个的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.07,0:41:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克在安全地点 你动不了他 这一切都结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.34,0:41:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的生活 所有谎言和伪装
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.44,0:41:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要告诉我这一切的真相
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.18,0:41:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如你到底是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.51,0:41:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底怎么回事 我要你全盘托出
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.62,0:42:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我们的生活
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.52,0:42:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切并没有结束 莎拉
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.65,0:42:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还差得远呢
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.42,0:42:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克也从未陷入过险境
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.54,0:42:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱他
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.46,0:42:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.12,0:42:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我养育了他
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.28,0:42:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.86,0:42:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不 是你做了什么 莎拉
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.77,0:42:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切本可以避免
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.51,0:42:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在朋友家睡得好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.81,0:42:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.85,0:42:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈会来接我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.48,0:42:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会的 少爷
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.39,0:42:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.42,0:42:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的希腊南丁格尔之行直接领我找到了他
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.03,0:42:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以... 这都是你造成的 莎拉
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.60,0:42:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让海瑟帮忙的计划也是行不通的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.93,0:42:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我儿子在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.20,0:42:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我手里
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.54,0:42:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于我是不是必须得威胁他...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:58.24,0:43:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我并不想这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.18,0:43:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全取决于你是否会把枪放下
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(33.149,216.075)\fs13\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H14&\4c&H000000&\4a&HFF&\fsp1.5\3c&H000000&\3a&H00&\4c&H000000&\4a&H00&} {\4c&H000000&\3c&H000000&\3a&H64&\c&HFFFFFF&\1a&H00&\4a&HFF&}扫扫加微信
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(480,0)\fs14\4c&H000000&\4a&HFF&\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\t(0,2000,\fs16)\pos(186.6,254.4)}4月5日起 每周三\N{\fs14}{\c&HFFFFFF&}即刻APP 特约 @大家字幕组 诚意制作\N{\fs14}在此感谢多年来为了剧迷默默付出的原创字幕组们！
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}{\fs14\fs14\fs14\fs14\fn微软雅黑\fs16\b1\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&}本字幕由{\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}大家字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&}原创翻译\N{\fs14}{\fs14\fs14\fs14\fs14}彼以国士待我 我以国士待之 用过免费优质字幕服务\N{\fs14}{\fs14\fs14\fs14\fs14}而又有能力的人 有义务将这个免费服务做下去 若有心加入我们\N{\fs14}{\fs14\fs14\fs14\fs14\c&H3934FF&\1a&H00&}请联系QQ群：428872140
