1
00:00:02,410 --> 00:00:03,620
Don't you have a job or something?

2
00:00:03,700 --> 00:00:04,890
Yeah, on a freelance cargo ship.

3
00:00:04,990 --> 00:00:06,690
We go to Hong Kong, Spain,

4
00:00:06,800 --> 00:00:08,760
Buenos Aires, basically wherever the boss tells us.

5
00:00:08,840 --> 00:00:10,360
Corrupt son of a bitch.

6
00:00:10,470 --> 00:00:12,280
We've awoken something, something people are trying to

7
00:00:12,360 --> 00:00:13,330
hide about Michael.

8
00:00:13,440 --> 00:00:14,870
Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?

9
00:00:14,970 --> 00:00:16,240
A psychopath.

10
00:00:16,340 --> 00:00:18,010
A frustrated policy wonk

11
00:00:18,110 --> 00:00:20,110
in the CIA who created a cell

12
00:00:20,210 --> 00:00:23,210
within the CIA called 21-Void.

13
00:00:23,310 --> 00:00:24,750
And they needed my help

14
00:00:24,850 --> 00:00:25,980
breaking out people in prison

15
00:00:26,080 --> 00:00:27,820
all over the world.

16
00:00:27,850 --> 00:00:29,120
Before he was killed,

17
00:00:29,150 --> 00:00:30,850
Kellerman had been looking into 21-Void.

18
00:00:30,890 --> 00:00:32,120
I need you to look into the possibility

19
00:00:32,160 --> 00:00:34,520
that there was an insider involved.

20
00:00:34,560 --> 00:00:36,260
I wasn't expecting a call at this hour.

21
00:00:36,290 --> 00:00:37,560
I think we need to meet soon.

22
00:00:37,590 --> 00:00:39,360
I was looking for where the man went.

23
00:00:39,400 --> 00:00:40,430
What man, baby?

24
00:00:40,460 --> 00:00:41,700
The man that gave me this.

25
00:00:41,730 --> 00:00:42,860
Michael.

26
00:00:42,900 --> 00:00:45,130
What are you into?

27
00:00:45,170 --> 00:00:46,700
Just tell us where you're headed.

28
00:00:46,740 --> 00:00:49,170
300 miles across the desert, Phaeacia.

29
00:00:49,210 --> 00:00:51,140
Autonomous zone. No ISIL.

30
00:00:51,170 --> 00:00:52,340
I can lead you there.

31
00:00:52,380 --> 00:00:54,110
Phaeacia, we found it!

32
00:01:07,260 --> 00:01:10,960
Back in the city, I told you you would die.

33
00:01:10,990 --> 00:01:12,030
Michael.

34
00:01:12,060 --> 00:01:13,860
He poisoned me.

35
00:01:37,650 --> 00:01:41,220
It's incredible how good you've gotten at drawing, Mike.

36
00:01:41,260 --> 00:01:43,890
Really, that's...

37
00:01:43,930 --> 00:01:45,830
that's so good.

38
00:01:45,860 --> 00:01:48,230
It's a Greek hero.

39
00:01:48,260 --> 00:01:49,860
He looks hurt.

40
00:01:49,900 --> 00:01:52,300
They all get hurt sooner or later.

41
00:01:52,340 --> 00:01:55,170
That's what's great about Greek heroes,

42
00:01:55,200 --> 00:01:58,270
they're real, not supermen.

43
00:01:58,310 --> 00:02:00,210
They get hurt.

44
00:02:00,240 --> 00:02:01,610
They can die.

45
00:02:10,920 --> 00:02:13,020
Hey, I'm sorry, buddy, last little bit.

46
00:02:13,060 --> 00:02:15,060
I got to keep it clean, you know?

47
00:02:15,090 --> 00:02:16,720
It's looking much better though, okay?

48
00:02:16,760 --> 00:02:18,760
You're doing good. You just hang in there, buddy.

49
00:02:19,560 --> 00:02:20,790
How we doing?

50
00:02:20,830 --> 00:02:22,460
Got something.

51
00:02:22,500 --> 00:02:24,180
Our friend over there has a boat.

52
00:02:24,260 --> 00:02:26,400
He's making a smuggling run to Greece.

53
00:02:26,440 --> 00:02:29,370
He says he can take your brother to a first world doctor.

54
00:02:29,410 --> 00:02:31,570
First world thinks he's Kaniel Outis.

55
00:02:31,610 --> 00:02:33,110
They'll arrest him on sight.

56
00:02:33,140 --> 00:02:34,580
So?

57
00:02:34,610 --> 00:02:35,910
What's the alternative, let him die?

58
00:02:35,950 --> 00:02:37,280
What kind of a brother are you?

59
00:02:39,880 --> 00:02:41,150
You say something like that again,

60
00:02:41,180 --> 00:02:42,950
I swear to God, I'll kill you.

61
00:02:49,560 --> 00:02:51,660
There might be a third option.

62
00:03:00,370 --> 00:03:02,600
So how was your first day back?

63
00:03:04,170 --> 00:03:06,610
I have to say, it's never been so rewarding

64
00:03:06,640 --> 00:03:07,840
to teach game theory to the tops

65
00:03:07,880 --> 00:03:09,280
of a bunch of 18-year-olds' heads

66
00:03:09,310 --> 00:03:10,910
while they're busy sexting each other.

67
00:03:13,480 --> 00:03:14,880
But...

68
00:03:14,920 --> 00:03:17,480
normalcy's threatening to come back,

69
00:03:17,520 --> 00:03:19,720
and I say cheers to that.

70
00:03:19,760 --> 00:03:21,060
Cheers to that.

71
00:03:22,790 --> 00:03:24,390
Come on, let's sit outside.

72
00:03:26,160 --> 00:03:27,800
I'll be right there.

73
00:03:33,170 --> 00:03:34,440
Hello?

74
00:03:34,470 --> 00:03:36,640
We found Michael.

75
00:03:36,670 --> 00:03:39,110
Is he our Michael?

76
00:03:39,170 --> 00:03:40,690
Yes, Sara.

77
00:03:42,760 --> 00:03:45,660
Sara, listen, he's been poisoned.

78
00:03:45,700 --> 00:03:46,900
We think it's antifreeze.

79
00:03:46,930 --> 00:03:48,170
He's lost a lot of blood.

80
00:03:48,200 --> 00:03:50,500
He needs a lot of blood.

81
00:03:50,540 --> 00:03:51,940
Okay.

82
00:03:51,970 --> 00:03:53,540
He needs a lot of things if it's antifreeze.

83
00:03:53,570 --> 00:03:54,810
Listen, uh,

84
00:03:54,840 --> 00:03:56,510
we're heading to Greece.

85
00:03:56,540 --> 00:03:58,740
Is there any way we can get some medical help off the books?

86
00:03:58,780 --> 00:04:00,380
No, no, no, no, no, this isn't the kind of thing

87
00:04:00,410 --> 00:04:01,950
that you want to do off the books.

88
00:04:01,980 --> 00:04:05,150
Listen, Lincoln, he's gonna need a transfusion.

89
00:04:05,180 --> 00:04:06,880
Michael's B negative, okay?

90
00:04:06,920 --> 00:04:09,920
It's maybe one percent of the population with that blood type.

91
00:04:09,960 --> 00:04:11,690
You won't find it where you're going,

92
00:04:11,720 --> 00:04:13,720
and he won't make it while you look.

93
00:04:15,960 --> 00:04:19,100
Unless it comes to you.

94
00:04:19,130 --> 00:04:20,500
I'll call you back.

95
00:04:22,200 --> 00:04:24,400
Hey, what's going on?

96
00:04:24,440 --> 00:04:26,000
I, uh...

97
00:04:26,040 --> 00:04:27,910
I got to go.

98
00:04:27,940 --> 00:04:29,840
You got to go?

99
00:04:29,880 --> 00:04:31,280
‭Go where?

100
00:04:31,310 --> 00:04:32,710
To Crete.

101
00:04:33,850 --> 00:04:35,250
Michael, um,

102
00:04:35,280 --> 00:04:36,880
they found him.

103
00:04:36,920 --> 00:04:38,320
He's alive.

104
00:04:38,350 --> 00:04:39,550
He's poisoned.

105
00:04:39,590 --> 00:04:41,950
Michael? Your ex, Michael?

106
00:04:41,990 --> 00:04:43,290
Yeah.

107
00:04:43,320 --> 00:04:44,460
Wait, hold on a second,

108
00:04:44,490 --> 00:04:46,860
he really is alive?

109
00:04:46,890 --> 00:04:48,390
He contacted you just now?

110
00:04:48,430 --> 00:04:51,860
Yeah, and, uh, and he needs help,

111
00:04:51,900 --> 00:04:55,970
and I think I'm the only one that can help him.

112
00:04:57,580 --> 00:05:00,770
yeah, I can get there faster on a plane than they can on a boat.

113
00:05:00,810 --> 00:05:03,410
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Sara?

114
00:05:03,440 --> 00:05:05,280
Y-You don't owe him that.

115
00:05:05,310 --> 00:05:07,240
You don't know what you'd be walking into. It's not safe.

116
00:05:07,280 --> 00:05:08,650
I'll be fine. I don't have a choice.

117
00:05:08,680 --> 00:05:09,980
I...

118
00:05:10,020 --> 00:05:11,720
This has been a hell of a week.

119
00:05:14,220 --> 00:05:16,120
Okay, look, I know you've got a million questions,

120
00:05:16,160 --> 00:05:17,990
just like I do, okay?

121
00:05:18,020 --> 00:05:20,520
I can't look my son in the eye

122
00:05:20,560 --> 00:05:22,630
and tell him that I let his father die

123
00:05:22,660 --> 00:05:24,960
when I could've tried to save him.

124
00:05:25,000 --> 00:05:26,330
A father he's never met.

125
00:05:26,370 --> 00:05:28,930
I can't do that.

126
00:05:28,970 --> 00:05:30,900
And if I told you not to go?

127
00:05:34,470 --> 00:05:36,110
"If's" A big word in that sentence.

128
00:05:36,140 --> 00:05:38,280
Jacob, are you telling me not to go?

129
00:05:41,610 --> 00:05:43,150
No.

130
00:05:43,180 --> 00:05:45,150
No, of course not.

131
00:05:45,180 --> 00:05:47,150
Okay.

132
00:05:58,260 --> 00:06:00,800
Should've left her out of this, Linc.

133
00:06:00,830 --> 00:06:03,370
Shut up. You're about to see the wife you haven't seen

134
00:06:03,400 --> 00:06:05,040
in seven years.

135
00:06:06,970 --> 00:06:08,870
- I got you, I got you. - Cast off.

136
00:06:08,910 --> 00:06:10,710
You're ready.

137
00:06:10,740 --> 00:06:12,710
What do you mean?

138
00:06:14,650 --> 00:06:18,420
Been locked up for longer than I can remember.

139
00:06:18,450 --> 00:06:20,380
Before Ogygia, it was my apartment, my head

140
00:06:20,420 --> 00:06:22,450
and my phone.

141
00:06:22,490 --> 00:06:23,990
Walls all around me.

142
00:06:24,020 --> 00:06:27,160
Couldn't see the world.

143
00:06:29,860 --> 00:06:31,360
I like it here.

144
00:06:31,400 --> 00:06:32,800
No walls.

145
00:06:32,830 --> 00:06:36,370
Freedom, like I haven't had in a long time.

146
00:06:36,400 --> 00:06:39,070
I can start over.

147
00:06:39,110 --> 00:06:42,070
And unless you say you need me,

148
00:06:42,110 --> 00:06:44,040
I'd like to stay.

149
00:06:44,080 --> 00:06:46,580
You're a free man, Ja.

150
00:06:46,610 --> 00:06:48,580
The choice is yours.

151
00:06:49,720 --> 00:06:52,580
I owe you my life.

152
00:06:52,620 --> 00:06:54,920
You gave me back the world.

153
00:06:58,120 --> 00:06:59,920
Get him healthy. Get safe.

154
00:06:59,960 --> 00:07:01,990
Yeah, I will.

155
00:07:02,030 --> 00:07:03,830
See you.

156
00:07:07,400 --> 00:07:08,600
Hey, hey, hey.

157
00:07:08,630 --> 00:07:10,070
I got to know,

158
00:07:10,100 --> 00:07:13,500
you really got Freddie Mercury's ashes?

159
00:07:13,540 --> 00:07:17,270
Is it true Keith Richards snorted his dead father's ashes?

160
00:07:17,310 --> 00:07:18,780
I don't know.

161
00:07:19,910 --> 00:07:22,110
Exactly.

162
00:07:22,150 --> 00:07:23,910
Keep alive.

163
00:07:23,950 --> 00:07:26,080
You too, man.

164
00:07:34,330 --> 00:07:36,730
Linc,

165
00:07:36,760 --> 00:07:38,560
how far is it to Greece?

166
00:07:38,600 --> 00:07:40,630
12 hours.

167
00:07:40,670 --> 00:07:42,230
Sara's gonna be there in 12.

168
00:07:42,270 --> 00:07:45,940
I don't think I have 12 hours in me.

169
00:09:03,460 --> 00:09:06,900
I was right, we got problems.

170
00:09:06,940 --> 00:09:11,010
Apparently, State Department is asking questions about 21-Void

171
00:09:11,040 --> 00:09:13,380
after our visit to NSA yesterday.

172
00:09:13,410 --> 00:09:15,280
They have no viable information.

173
00:09:16,410 --> 00:09:18,450
21-Void doesn't exist.

174
00:09:18,480 --> 00:09:19,880
Poseidon will clean house.

175
00:09:19,920 --> 00:09:22,050
The problem's not going away.

176
00:09:22,090 --> 00:09:23,290
That State Department agent wants to meet

177
00:09:23,320 --> 00:09:24,790
as soon as we land.

178
00:09:35,470 --> 00:09:37,730
Chania, please?

179
00:09:37,770 --> 00:09:39,030
Thank you.

180
00:09:54,490 --> 00:09:56,250
It is safe here.

181
00:09:56,290 --> 00:09:57,820
I use when I come.

182
00:09:57,860 --> 00:10:01,460
You got any food for him?

183
00:10:01,490 --> 00:10:02,660
Come, it's in the boat.

184
00:10:02,690 --> 00:10:05,260
Great, thank you.

185
00:10:05,300 --> 00:10:07,000
Keep his spirits up.

186
00:10:07,030 --> 00:10:10,000
All right, man.

187
00:10:12,970 --> 00:10:16,340
Oh, man.

188
00:10:19,910 --> 00:10:21,810
Got to hang in there, buddy, huh?

189
00:10:24,450 --> 00:10:28,480
Still got a lot of things to tell me, you know?

190
00:10:31,460 --> 00:10:33,360
You gonna tell me why I'm your whip hand.

191
00:10:33,390 --> 00:10:35,520
Remember?

192
00:10:42,730 --> 00:10:44,530
I got a lot invested in you.

193
00:10:47,310 --> 00:10:50,140
You can't die on me now, Michael, you know?

194
00:10:51,510 --> 00:10:54,280
Called you Michael.

195
00:10:54,310 --> 00:10:58,950
The first... first time I ever really known your name,

196
00:10:58,980 --> 00:11:01,520
even though I feel like...

197
00:11:03,390 --> 00:11:06,190
I feel like we've been brothers since we met, you know?

198
00:11:11,900 --> 00:11:14,200
You know, with... with Linc here...

199
00:11:17,900 --> 00:11:20,900
...it was the first time I ever felt like an outsider with you.

200
00:11:20,940 --> 00:11:23,110
You know, like...

201
00:11:23,140 --> 00:11:25,940
like I lost...

202
00:11:25,980 --> 00:11:27,810
part of my family or something.

203
00:11:27,850 --> 00:11:31,980
So, you see, Michael, you can't die.

204
00:11:36,120 --> 00:11:38,420
Please?

205
00:12:29,410 --> 00:12:32,310
Linc.

206
00:12:58,340 --> 00:13:00,570
I missed you.

207
00:13:09,880 --> 00:13:12,610
I'm gonna fix you up.

208
00:13:12,650 --> 00:13:14,780
And then we'll talk, okay?

209
00:13:17,120 --> 00:13:19,490
I'm gonna make you okay.

210
00:13:21,630 --> 00:13:23,490
No.

211
00:13:24,560 --> 00:13:26,830
shh, shh, shh, it's okay.

212
00:13:28,030 --> 00:13:30,030
Hey, Lincoln, uh,

213
00:13:30,070 --> 00:13:32,000
would you pass me that coatrack?

214
00:13:32,040 --> 00:13:34,070
Could I grab the chair, please?

215
00:13:35,840 --> 00:13:37,340
Thanks.

216
00:13:58,200 --> 00:14:00,230
We'll do a transfusion.

217
00:14:04,700 --> 00:14:05,900
I'm O negative.

218
00:14:05,940 --> 00:14:08,500
It's the universal donor.

219
00:14:08,540 --> 00:14:11,410
Turns out it's the only other blood type I could've given him.

220
00:14:14,040 --> 00:14:16,040
Maybe there's something to destiny, huh?

221
00:14:20,180 --> 00:14:23,190
Is he gonna live?

222
00:14:23,220 --> 00:14:25,890
Yeah.

223
00:14:25,920 --> 00:14:28,190
Yeah, he'll live.

224
00:14:28,230 --> 00:14:30,830
Give him a couple hours.

225
00:14:30,860 --> 00:14:33,260
He's strong.

226
00:14:36,500 --> 00:14:39,800
We'll, uh... we'll give you a minute.

227
00:14:39,840 --> 00:14:41,740
Yeah.

228
00:14:41,770 --> 00:14:44,940
I'm right here.

229
00:14:44,980 --> 00:14:46,710
I'm right here.

230
00:14:51,750 --> 00:14:54,280
We need to work out a way to get off this island.

231
00:15:00,960 --> 00:15:03,590
What I said...

232
00:15:03,630 --> 00:15:07,260
um, about you...

233
00:15:07,300 --> 00:15:09,600
I was wrong.

234
00:15:13,370 --> 00:15:14,800
A man would be lucky to have a brother

235
00:15:14,840 --> 00:15:16,910
cares as much as you, you know?

236
00:15:18,780 --> 00:15:20,740
Wife like that...

237
00:15:22,510 --> 00:15:24,610
...family.

238
00:15:27,650 --> 00:15:29,720
I wouldn't call it luck.

239
00:15:29,750 --> 00:15:32,450
You've been through what we've been through.

240
00:15:32,490 --> 00:15:34,290
You're family now.

241
00:15:37,860 --> 00:15:39,230
I'll drink to that.

242
00:15:39,260 --> 00:15:41,660
Yeah.

243
00:15:43,070 --> 00:15:44,670
Flying's really out of the question?

244
00:15:44,700 --> 00:15:45,830
Yeah.

245
00:15:45,870 --> 00:15:49,770
Airports are worse than hospitals.

246
00:15:49,810 --> 00:15:52,810
And once the name Kaniel Outis is radioactive,

247
00:15:52,840 --> 00:15:54,910
they'll shoot him on sight.

248
00:15:56,180 --> 00:15:58,510
So another boat?

249
00:15:58,550 --> 00:16:00,550
Across the Atlantic?

250
00:16:00,580 --> 00:16:05,790
Mm, I'm no sailor, but I know that no boat in that harbor

251
00:16:05,820 --> 00:16:08,290
is gonna get us that far.

252
00:16:08,330 --> 00:16:09,830
We need a big boat.

253
00:16:11,500 --> 00:16:15,930
One that doesn't mind a radioactive cargo, you know?

254
00:16:30,310 --> 00:16:34,020
Hey there, I wanted to follow up on our conversation.

255
00:16:34,050 --> 00:16:35,750
Obviously, the CIA and State,

256
00:16:35,790 --> 00:16:37,790
we've been sharing information on Kaniel Outis,

257
00:16:37,820 --> 00:16:40,020
but my question for you is:

258
00:16:40,060 --> 00:16:41,720
Outis killed Abu Ramal,

259
00:16:41,760 --> 00:16:44,130
did the country a service.

260
00:16:44,160 --> 00:16:46,760
So why were you still at NSA yesterday,

261
00:16:46,800 --> 00:16:48,800
trying to kill him?

262
00:16:48,830 --> 00:16:50,830
Why don't we get off the tarmac?

263
00:16:50,870 --> 00:16:53,170
We'll share what we can about our investigation.

264
00:16:54,540 --> 00:16:57,240
This is all just bureaucratic miscommunication.

265
00:16:57,270 --> 00:16:59,470
We can iron it out.

266
00:16:59,510 --> 00:17:01,840
So you know, we checked with CIA.

267
00:17:01,880 --> 00:17:05,150
The CIA didn't sanction your visit to NSA yesterday.

268
00:17:05,180 --> 00:17:06,950
No one even knew you were there.

269
00:17:06,980 --> 00:17:09,480
Who are you working for, really?

270
00:17:09,520 --> 00:17:12,020
And why were you trying to take out Kaniel Outis?

271
00:17:20,630 --> 00:17:23,100
Never thought I'd see this face again.

272
00:17:23,130 --> 00:17:25,600
You weren't supposed to.

273
00:17:27,200 --> 00:17:29,070
Why?

274
00:17:30,910 --> 00:17:34,340
I'll tell you everything you want to know.

275
00:17:34,380 --> 00:17:36,880
But first, I need something from you.

276
00:17:36,910 --> 00:17:38,750
Anything.

277
00:17:40,380 --> 00:17:43,290
A picture of my son.

278
00:17:46,460 --> 00:17:48,290
We weren't at NSA yesterday.

279
00:17:48,330 --> 00:17:50,530
I'm telling you, this is a mistake.

280
00:17:50,560 --> 00:17:52,160
And it's a mistake to lie to me.

281
00:17:52,200 --> 00:17:53,930
I can have you prosecuted.

282
00:17:53,960 --> 00:17:57,870
I have a contact at the NSA and she gave me proof.

283
00:17:57,900 --> 00:18:00,640
You're not calling him Junior, are you?

284
00:18:00,670 --> 00:18:03,810
I promised you I would never do that.

285
00:18:05,040 --> 00:18:06,980
He's an amazing kid.

286
00:18:08,610 --> 00:18:10,380
He's just like you.

287
00:18:19,190 --> 00:18:20,960
What's wrong?

288
00:18:33,100 --> 00:18:34,640
It's him.

289
00:18:40,280 --> 00:18:42,510
Your husband.

290
00:18:42,550 --> 00:18:44,610
Jacob?

291
00:18:44,650 --> 00:18:46,920
Jacob.

292
00:18:54,190 --> 00:18:56,490
Jacob is Poseidon.

293
00:19:04,400 --> 00:19:06,530
I knewt. I wasn't crazy.

294
00:19:06,630 --> 00:19:10,030
I caught him lying, but he-he--

295
00:19:10,140 --> 00:19:11,670
oh, God, he covered it so well.

296
00:19:11,770 --> 00:19:14,710
He was... honest and hurt,

297
00:19:14,810 --> 00:19:16,340
and I bought it.

298
00:19:16,440 --> 00:19:17,780
Who is he?

299
00:19:17,880 --> 00:19:19,540
Really?

300
00:19:19,650 --> 00:19:23,010
He's a CIA operative, deep cover.

301
00:19:23,120 --> 00:19:25,280
He runs a splinter cell called 21-Void.

302
00:19:25,380 --> 00:19:27,650
What does this have to do with you?

303
00:19:27,750 --> 00:19:30,390
He targeted me for my skills,

304
00:19:30,490 --> 00:19:31,960
blackmailed me.

305
00:19:32,060 --> 00:19:34,430
He told me if I didn't agree to come work for him,

306
00:19:34,530 --> 00:19:36,230
he'd go after you and Linc,

307
00:19:36,330 --> 00:19:38,700
put you both in jail.

308
00:19:39,250 --> 00:19:41,250
And then he proved it to me.

309
00:19:43,390 --> 00:19:45,820
He said I could never see either one of you again.

310
00:19:46,730 --> 00:19:48,520
Or Mike.

311
00:19:48,620 --> 00:19:50,560
Made me fake my death.

312
00:19:50,660 --> 00:19:53,190
And then he just used me.

313
00:19:53,300 --> 00:19:54,730
He married me.

314
00:19:54,830 --> 00:19:56,560
If I'd known he was your husband, I swear...

315
00:19:56,670 --> 00:19:57,660
No, no, no, no, no,

316
00:19:57,770 --> 00:19:59,700
this is not on you.

317
00:19:59,800 --> 00:20:01,840
I...

318
00:20:03,640 --> 00:20:05,910
Why now? Why did you come back now?

319
00:20:06,010 --> 00:20:08,110
The origami...

320
00:20:09,880 --> 00:20:12,550
Four years ago, he betrayed me

321
00:20:12,650 --> 00:20:15,180
and now I know why.

322
00:20:15,280 --> 00:20:18,690
He wanted me out of the way...

323
00:20:18,790 --> 00:20:20,520
so he could have you.

324
00:20:21,490 --> 00:20:23,790
How did he betray you?

325
00:20:23,890 --> 00:20:26,060
He set a meeting.

326
00:20:26,160 --> 00:20:28,960
We were supposed to discuss my next assignment.

327
00:20:29,060 --> 00:20:31,600
What he didn't tell me was that

328
00:20:31,700 --> 00:20:33,070
we were meeting a man named Harlan Gaines,

329
00:20:33,170 --> 00:20:35,970
a deputy director of the CIA.

330
00:20:36,070 --> 00:20:38,170
Gaines was investigating 21-Void.

331
00:20:38,270 --> 00:20:40,470
Looking for the traitor behind it.

332
00:20:40,580 --> 00:20:44,610
That's when I knew my work wasn't sanctioned by the CIA.

333
00:20:44,710 --> 00:20:47,850
Poseidon shot and killed Gaines that night,

334
00:20:47,950 --> 00:20:49,980
to stop the investigation.

335
00:20:53,560 --> 00:20:54,860
He told me to move the body,

336
00:20:54,960 --> 00:20:57,290
make it look like it never happened.

337
00:20:57,390 --> 00:20:59,560
I've seen the photos of that part, they're damning.

338
00:20:59,660 --> 00:21:02,300
He chose images that showed me moving Gaines' body,

339
00:21:02,400 --> 00:21:05,470
eliminated the ones that incriminated himself.

340
00:21:05,570 --> 00:21:08,540
I knew I was being set up.

341
00:21:08,640 --> 00:21:10,470
He was tightening his control over me,

342
00:21:10,570 --> 00:21:13,840
but there was nothing I could do.

343
00:21:13,940 --> 00:21:16,810
At least, that's what he thought.

344
00:21:16,910 --> 00:21:19,610
When I knew Poseidon had gone rogue

345
00:21:19,720 --> 00:21:22,080
and was operating outside the CIA,

346
00:21:22,180 --> 00:21:24,680
that's when I started my plan to get back to you.

347
00:21:25,620 --> 00:21:26,900
You're not.

348
00:21:26,990 --> 00:21:28,600
Some other man has your--

349
00:21:28,990 --> 00:21:30,760
your face, your past, your whole life.

350
00:21:30,860 --> 00:21:33,530
Sara, there is a plan to make this right,

351
00:21:33,630 --> 00:21:36,360
to protect our family.

352
00:21:38,500 --> 00:21:41,200
Michael, he's with our son right now.

353
00:21:41,300 --> 00:21:44,470
He's with Mike.

354
00:21:44,570 --> 00:21:47,440
I, uh, look, I have to go.

355
00:21:51,180 --> 00:21:52,980
Hey, Noah, you gonna build us a boat?

356
00:21:53,080 --> 00:21:56,720
Nope. I'm gonna do one better.

357
00:21:56,820 --> 00:21:58,390
Who you calling?

358
00:21:59,520 --> 00:22:02,040
A friend who actually has a boat.

359
00:22:11,200 --> 00:22:12,600
Hello?

360
00:22:12,700 --> 00:22:13,800
Sucre, it's me.

361
00:22:13,900 --> 00:22:15,840
Linc? I thought the Middle East

362
00:22:15,940 --> 00:22:17,100
was gonna swallow you up, man.

363
00:22:17,210 --> 00:22:20,010
Where's Michael? Did you find him?

364
00:22:20,110 --> 00:22:22,080
Listen, that's why I'm calling.

365
00:22:22,180 --> 00:22:23,740
We're on the island of Crete.

366
00:22:23,850 --> 00:22:25,680
We need a low profile ride back to the States.

367
00:22:25,780 --> 00:22:27,350
I would love to help,

368
00:22:27,450 --> 00:22:29,150
but we're on the other side of the world, brother.

369
00:22:29,250 --> 00:22:30,820
We just dropped a load in Morocco.

370
00:22:30,920 --> 00:22:33,320
What are you talking about? Morocco's near Crete.

371
00:22:33,420 --> 00:22:36,190
Yeah, I know, of course it is,

372
00:22:36,290 --> 00:22:38,430
but what I mean is it's not my ship.

373
00:22:38,530 --> 00:22:41,260
Yeah, but what would it cost to hitch a ride?

374
00:22:41,360 --> 00:22:42,960
You can't hitch a ride.

375
00:22:43,070 --> 00:22:44,700
You have to rent the whole ship.

376
00:22:44,800 --> 00:22:47,130
The boss charges 50K a leg, Linc.

377
00:22:47,240 --> 00:22:49,370
You want to get back to the States, it's 50K.

378
00:22:49,470 --> 00:22:50,600
50k?

379
00:22:50,710 --> 00:22:52,910
We're just trying to get home.

380
00:22:53,010 --> 00:22:55,010
You know we don't have that kind of cash.

381
00:22:56,650 --> 00:22:58,010
You do now.

382
00:22:59,310 --> 00:23:00,750
Here, this was my grandmother's.

383
00:23:00,850 --> 00:23:02,150
It's an heirloom worth at least that.

384
00:23:06,490 --> 00:23:08,790
I can't think of a better use for it.

385
00:23:09,690 --> 00:23:11,390
Thank you.

386
00:23:11,490 --> 00:23:15,760
We got it, Sucre. Get to Crete.

387
00:23:17,570 --> 00:23:19,800
He's not gonna hurt Mike,

388
00:23:19,820 --> 00:23:22,440
not unless he suspects you know who he really is.

389
00:23:22,540 --> 00:23:23,900
If you remove his mask,

390
00:23:24,010 --> 00:23:25,570
he'll lash out.

391
00:23:25,670 --> 00:23:27,340
You know him better than I do.

392
00:23:27,440 --> 00:23:29,110
That's the point, no one knows him.

393
00:23:29,210 --> 00:23:30,910
So, what do I do?

394
00:23:31,010 --> 00:23:33,550
You play his game. You wear your own mask.

395
00:23:33,650 --> 00:23:36,580
As soon as you get a chance to get away with Mike,

396
00:23:36,690 --> 00:23:40,220
you take it, disappear.

397
00:23:40,320 --> 00:23:42,420
I'll get to the States as soon as I can.

398
00:23:42,520 --> 00:23:45,130
I'll find you.

399
00:23:45,230 --> 00:23:46,890
You're looking better.

400
00:23:47,000 --> 00:23:48,730
A little grayer, but better.

401
00:23:48,830 --> 00:23:51,870
I have an amazing doctor on call.

402
00:23:58,670 --> 00:24:01,540
I will wear the mask.

403
00:24:01,640 --> 00:24:04,080
I will play his game...

404
00:24:04,180 --> 00:24:07,850
and if he hurts our son I'll kill him.

405
00:24:10,750 --> 00:24:12,250
I can't...

406
00:24:29,440 --> 00:24:32,870
Please come back to us.

407
00:24:49,690 --> 00:24:51,590
She's leaving Crete alone,

408
00:24:51,690 --> 00:24:54,830
which means she left Outis behind, and he'll try to follow,

409
00:24:54,930 --> 00:24:56,700
return to the U.S. In the next day or two.

410
00:24:56,700 --> 00:24:58,670
Who called? It can only be by ship or plane, so plaster his face

411
00:24:58,690 --> 00:25:01,940
on all maritime and air channels,

412
00:25:01,950 --> 00:25:03,540
focusing on all vessels departing from Crete

413
00:25:03,640 --> 00:25:04,600
in the next 48 hours.

414
00:25:04,710 --> 00:25:06,370
He's got to be on one.

415
00:25:06,480 --> 00:25:08,810
He can't make it back inside the country. Jacob?

416
00:25:09,850 --> 00:25:11,780
Was that Mommy?

417
00:25:14,180 --> 00:25:18,390
Yes. Mommy's on her way home.

418
00:25:29,550 --> 00:25:31,550
Michael Scofield.

419
00:25:32,890 --> 00:25:35,550
My man, you got more lives than anyone.

420
00:25:36,790 --> 00:25:38,420
Think I might've used them all up.

421
00:25:39,290 --> 00:25:40,890
A damn phoenix.

422
00:25:40,930 --> 00:25:42,530
I can't believe it.

423
00:25:42,560 --> 00:25:44,100
I want to hear every damn thing

424
00:25:44,130 --> 00:25:45,830
that's happened to you since you died.

425
00:25:45,870 --> 00:25:47,530
Papi, you're alive?

426
00:25:50,670 --> 00:25:52,170
The skipper is a corrupt bastard.

427
00:25:52,210 --> 00:25:53,770
Don't mess with him. He's got guns in the hold,

428
00:25:53,810 --> 00:25:56,810
- all kinds of contraband. - Captain.

429
00:25:59,050 --> 00:26:00,850
Here's the cargo I was telling you about.

430
00:26:00,880 --> 00:26:02,710
Pay up.

431
00:26:02,750 --> 00:26:04,920
Where's the 50K?

432
00:26:04,950 --> 00:26:06,690
Here.

433
00:26:06,720 --> 00:26:09,590
I said cash.

434
00:26:09,620 --> 00:26:11,920
It's a sapphire, six carats,

435
00:26:11,960 --> 00:26:15,560
flawless, surrounded by 2.5 carats of bezeled diamonds.

436
00:26:15,600 --> 00:26:17,500
Street value is 125K.

437
00:26:17,530 --> 00:26:21,930
You can pawn it for half that and still make a profit.

438
00:26:30,210 --> 00:26:31,380
If it's fake,

439
00:26:31,410 --> 00:26:33,950
you go under the sea.

440
00:26:36,420 --> 00:26:39,350
A boat is the last place I expected to find you, buddy.

441
00:26:39,390 --> 00:26:40,950
I thought you hated the water.

442
00:26:40,990 --> 00:26:44,220
Yeah, you remember, but I got a record.

443
00:26:44,260 --> 00:26:46,890
Not a lot of employers lined up to take a chance on me.

444
00:26:46,930 --> 00:26:49,330
Besides, this ship provides opportunities

445
00:26:49,360 --> 00:26:51,060
for my side business...

446
00:26:51,100 --> 00:26:53,030
which is the real reason I'm on this boat.

447
00:26:53,070 --> 00:26:55,000
This baby...

448
00:26:55,040 --> 00:26:57,170
houses my entire life savings.

449
00:26:57,200 --> 00:26:59,540
I'm telling you, it's gonna be huge.

450
00:26:59,570 --> 00:27:02,240
I'm a few months away from putting all this behind me.

451
00:27:02,280 --> 00:27:04,510
If you guys are lucky, I'll let you guys

452
00:27:04,550 --> 00:27:07,080
take one of my ladies for a spin.

453
00:27:09,480 --> 00:27:10,920
Huh?

454
00:27:11,820 --> 00:27:13,820
What, sex dolls?

455
00:27:13,850 --> 00:27:15,050
No, have some class, man.

456
00:27:15,090 --> 00:27:16,860
The term is inflatables, high quality,

457
00:27:16,890 --> 00:27:18,620
expensive, very lifelike.

458
00:27:20,690 --> 00:27:23,260
Huh?

459
00:27:40,680 --> 00:27:41,880
Hey, honey.

460
00:27:41,920 --> 00:27:44,050
Hey, you.

461
00:28:00,000 --> 00:28:01,270
Where's Mike?

462
00:28:01,300 --> 00:28:03,670
Asleep.

463
00:28:03,700 --> 00:28:04,700
Kid had a big day.

464
00:28:06,370 --> 00:28:08,540
Most important, though,

465
00:28:08,580 --> 00:28:10,080
how's Michael?

466
00:28:10,110 --> 00:28:12,180
Were you able to help him?

467
00:28:12,210 --> 00:28:16,720
I mean, he was barely alive when I got there.

468
00:28:16,750 --> 00:28:20,390
He, uh, slept most of the time.

469
00:28:20,420 --> 00:28:22,320
I... I did what I could for him. I, uh...

470
00:28:22,360 --> 00:28:26,290
I stabilized him, but he's changed.

471
00:28:26,330 --> 00:28:30,600
He, uh... he's just not the guy I knew.

472
00:28:30,630 --> 00:28:33,530
Hmm. ‭So, they dropped me at the airport and that was that.

473
00:28:33,570 --> 00:28:35,630
They?

474
00:28:35,670 --> 00:28:37,800
Linc and some other guy.

475
00:28:45,080 --> 00:28:47,410
Mike?

476
00:28:49,780 --> 00:28:51,320
Where's Mike?

477
00:28:51,350 --> 00:28:53,150
You said that he was asleep. ‭He is...

478
00:28:53,190 --> 00:28:55,690
at a friend's house, a sleepover.

479
00:28:55,720 --> 00:28:58,560
Okay. Which friend?

480
00:28:58,590 --> 00:28:59,890
He's at Patrick's house.

481
00:29:03,530 --> 00:29:05,700
What happened to your grandmother's ring?

482
00:29:06,770 --> 00:29:09,170
I'm such an idiot.

483
00:29:09,200 --> 00:29:11,070
I took it off on the way over for safekeeping,

484
00:29:11,100 --> 00:29:13,040
cause I didn't want it to get stolen,

485
00:29:13,070 --> 00:29:16,640
then when I looked for it on the way back it was gone.

486
00:29:16,680 --> 00:29:20,480
Screamed so loud they nearly threw me off the flight.

487
00:29:50,340 --> 00:29:51,780
Yeah?

488
00:29:51,810 --> 00:29:54,350
We spoke to our man at the Pentagon.

489
00:29:54,380 --> 00:29:55,950
A naval alert just went out.

490
00:29:55,980 --> 00:29:58,080
Kaniel Outis has been located

491
00:29:58,120 --> 00:30:00,690
on a cargo ship in the Mediterranean.

492
00:30:00,720 --> 00:30:02,650
It was reported by the ship's captain.

493
00:30:02,690 --> 00:30:04,320
What's the navy gonna do about it?

494
00:30:04,360 --> 00:30:06,420
The nearest LCS combat craft

495
00:30:06,460 --> 00:30:08,260
is moving to engage.

496
00:30:08,300 --> 00:30:09,830
SEAL team's been deployed.

497
00:30:09,860 --> 00:30:11,430
Orders?

498
00:30:11,470 --> 00:30:14,870
To seek and destroy Kaniel Outis.

499
00:30:14,900 --> 00:30:16,300
Good.

500
00:30:16,340 --> 00:30:18,070
We've done our job getting the message out.

501
00:30:18,110 --> 00:30:21,170
Now it's time for the SEALs to do theirs.

502
00:30:21,210 --> 00:30:24,010
My God.

503
00:30:25,150 --> 00:30:27,380
You've been through hell, my friend.

504
00:30:30,520 --> 00:30:32,250
Have some faith, papi.

505
00:30:32,290 --> 00:30:34,820
Thanks, papi.

506
00:30:36,320 --> 00:30:37,360
What about you, Linc?

507
00:30:38,760 --> 00:30:40,760
I think Linc's got a secret girlfriend,

508
00:30:40,790 --> 00:30:42,760
the pilot lady.

509
00:30:42,800 --> 00:30:44,130
She's not my lady.

510
00:30:44,160 --> 00:30:46,700
Maybe Sucre will set you up with one of his sex dolls.

511
00:30:46,730 --> 00:30:48,030
They're not dolls, man.

512
00:30:48,070 --> 00:30:49,570
Oh, sorry, inflatables.

513
00:30:49,600 --> 00:30:51,270
Look, let's just change the subject, please.

514
00:30:51,300 --> 00:30:54,040
You know, might be something to be said for settling down.

515
00:30:54,070 --> 00:30:57,480
Right, well... that's not in the cards.

516
00:31:03,880 --> 00:31:05,880
It's locked from the outside.

517
00:31:05,920 --> 00:31:06,950
They made you.

518
00:31:06,990 --> 00:31:08,950
You really are a wanted terrorist.

519
00:31:08,990 --> 00:31:10,190
What did the hell did you think he was saying?

520
00:31:10,220 --> 00:31:11,160
I thought it was an analogy.

521
00:31:11,190 --> 00:31:12,420
Oh, for God's sake.

522
00:31:12,460 --> 00:31:13,860
There's no other way

523
00:31:13,890 --> 00:31:16,030
out of this cabin.

524
00:31:19,830 --> 00:31:24,540
All crew to the top deck. All hands up.

525
00:31:24,570 --> 00:31:27,010
Comply or be fired on.

526
00:31:27,040 --> 00:31:30,880
This ship is now under the control of the U.S. Navy.

527
00:31:30,910 --> 00:31:31,780
Prepared to be boarded.

528
00:31:31,810 --> 00:31:33,450
We got company.

529
00:31:33,480 --> 00:31:34,710
I say we jump.

530
00:31:34,750 --> 00:31:35,880
That's a long way down.

531
00:31:35,920 --> 00:31:37,120
It's the only way out.

532
00:31:37,130 --> 00:31:37,940
It's too far.

533
00:31:37,980 --> 00:31:39,540
I have an idea...

534
00:31:41,320 --> 00:31:44,080
...but it's gonna hurt.

535
00:32:02,400 --> 00:32:04,300
Hello?

536
00:32:04,340 --> 00:32:06,140
Hey, Heather, it's me. Listen, I can't talk,

537
00:32:06,170 --> 00:32:08,340
but I need you to go pick up Mike right now, okay?

538
00:32:08,380 --> 00:32:09,810
Do you know where Patrick Monroe lives?

539
00:32:09,840 --> 00:32:10,810
Yeah.

540
00:32:10,840 --> 00:32:12,010
Okay.

541
00:32:12,050 --> 00:32:13,550
Listen, I'll explain later.

542
00:32:13,580 --> 00:32:15,410
Don't bring him back here, okay?

543
00:32:15,450 --> 00:32:17,550
Keep him with you. I'll be over as soon as I can.

544
00:32:17,580 --> 00:32:18,880
Can you do that for me?

545
00:32:18,920 --> 00:32:21,150
Uh, yeah. Uh, I'll leave right now.

546
00:32:21,190 --> 00:32:22,520
I-I-Is everything okay?

547
00:32:22,560 --> 00:32:23,620
No.

548
00:32:32,030 --> 00:32:33,370
Go.

549
00:32:35,840 --> 00:32:37,770
Six. The rest with me.

550
00:32:41,040 --> 00:32:42,270
Go.

551
00:32:48,450 --> 00:32:51,350
One, two, three, four.

552
00:32:53,690 --> 00:32:55,150
Go, go.

553
00:33:02,700 --> 00:33:04,730
I'll go left, you right.

554
00:33:13,340 --> 00:33:14,370
They went out the window!

555
00:33:14,410 --> 00:33:15,670
They went out the window!

556
00:33:15,710 --> 00:33:17,980
What do you see?

557
00:33:18,010 --> 00:33:19,510
No visual.

558
00:33:20,810 --> 00:33:23,850
Alpha One, Alpha Two to portside, now.

559
00:33:23,880 --> 00:33:26,380
Copy that.

560
00:33:28,320 --> 00:33:29,690
Okay!

561
00:33:29,720 --> 00:33:32,390
Take... Take it off!

562
00:33:32,430 --> 00:33:33,430
What's your name?

563
00:33:33,460 --> 00:33:35,260
Fernando.

564
00:33:35,300 --> 00:33:36,860
Fernando Sucre.

565
00:33:36,900 --> 00:33:39,000
I'm a member of this crew. Check the roster, man.

566
00:33:39,030 --> 00:33:40,830
I got no part in any of this.

567
00:33:40,870 --> 00:33:44,740
Check the roster for Fernando Sucre.

568
00:33:46,210 --> 00:33:48,830
Suspect seems to check out.

569
00:33:48,930 --> 00:33:50,380
Take him to the bridge.

570
00:33:50,410 --> 00:33:52,040
Yes, sir.

571
00:33:52,080 --> 00:33:54,450
Let's move.

572
00:33:58,490 --> 00:34:00,920
Absolutely no one gets off this ship, understand?

573
00:34:00,950 --> 00:34:02,250
Yes, sir.

574
00:34:16,940 --> 00:34:18,640
I don't know any Kaniel Outis.

575
00:34:18,670 --> 00:34:19,900
The guy's name is Scofield.

576
00:34:19,940 --> 00:34:21,170
Haven't seen him in years.

577
00:34:21,210 --> 00:34:23,210
He calls me, he says he needs a ride.

578
00:34:23,240 --> 00:34:26,180
We got active pursuit on engine deck.

579
00:34:26,210 --> 00:34:27,340
Watch him.

580
00:34:27,380 --> 00:34:29,910
The guy's name is Scofield!

581
00:34:33,520 --> 00:34:36,250
That's the door Sucre told us about.

582
00:34:37,160 --> 00:34:38,520
There they are!

583
00:34:38,560 --> 00:34:40,220
Freeze! Freeze!

584
00:34:41,760 --> 00:34:43,660
Look alive

585
00:34:43,700 --> 00:34:45,700
We've got them bottled up.

586
00:34:45,730 --> 00:34:48,500
Guys, come on! Hurry!

587
00:34:48,530 --> 00:34:49,600
Hurry!

588
00:34:49,640 --> 00:34:50,770
It's stuck!

589
00:34:50,800 --> 00:34:52,200
- Come on! - ‭It's stuck!

590
00:34:52,240 --> 00:34:54,300
It's stuck!

591
00:34:54,340 --> 00:34:55,710
Smoke them out, go!

592
00:35:07,090 --> 00:35:09,590
Tear gas.

593
00:35:09,620 --> 00:35:13,190
That hits the ventilation, it's gonna ruin my cargo.

594
00:35:16,160 --> 00:35:18,260
You've always been a loser, Sucre.

595
00:35:18,300 --> 00:35:19,600
Worst shipmate I ever hired.

596
00:35:19,630 --> 00:35:21,270
You brought this scum on board my ship.

597
00:35:21,300 --> 00:35:23,100
They're your friends. Where are they going?

598
00:35:23,140 --> 00:35:24,230
They're associates of associates.

599
00:35:24,270 --> 00:35:26,140
I haven't seen them in years.

600
00:35:26,170 --> 00:35:27,470
But that's a good point.

601
00:35:27,510 --> 00:35:30,010
Why don't you tell the nice SEAL here

602
00:35:30,040 --> 00:35:32,240
how you accepted payment for their passage?

603
00:35:37,150 --> 00:35:39,780
Maybe they're your friends, not mine.

604
00:35:39,820 --> 00:35:41,990
Okay, okay.

605
00:35:42,020 --> 00:35:45,590
I heard them say something about container 17.

606
00:35:52,500 --> 00:35:54,830
That container 17.

607
00:35:54,870 --> 00:35:58,700
The one with your super secret cargo, huh?

608
00:35:58,740 --> 00:36:00,200
Weapons and munitions?

609
00:36:00,240 --> 00:36:03,440
Vincent, tangos may be arming themselves.

610
00:36:03,480 --> 00:36:06,380
Man, they're not gonna like you if they find that, are they?

611
00:36:06,410 --> 00:36:08,080
Vincent.

612
00:36:08,110 --> 00:36:10,710
You might just end up on the terrorist watch list, too.

613
00:36:10,750 --> 00:36:11,720
Vincent, do you copy?

614
00:36:11,750 --> 00:36:13,650
Can't read you.

615
00:36:13,690 --> 00:36:17,520
Good-for-nothing Mexican. You planned this.

616
00:36:17,560 --> 00:36:18,690
Stay here.

617
00:36:27,570 --> 00:36:29,200
17's still sealed.

618
00:36:33,410 --> 00:36:34,740
Captain?

619
00:36:37,810 --> 00:36:40,380
I'm Puerto Rican.

620
00:36:44,350 --> 00:36:46,720
twelve o' clock ,You hear that?

621
00:36:53,860 --> 00:36:55,090
Come on!

622
00:37:00,750 --> 00:37:02,040
Go, go. Move!

623
00:37:06,680 --> 00:37:08,000
What's going on?

624
00:37:08,020 --> 00:37:08,970
The ship's changing course.

625
00:37:11,200 --> 00:37:12,830
I did it, papi.

626
00:37:12,860 --> 00:37:14,270
No going back now.

627
00:37:15,710 --> 00:37:18,710
See what their next move is.

628
00:37:31,420 --> 00:37:34,290
Do you remember our honeymoon?

629
00:37:38,930 --> 00:37:40,730
Yeah, of course.

630
00:37:40,770 --> 00:37:42,700
How you opened up.

631
00:37:42,730 --> 00:37:46,470
Told me you carried shame for what you did at Fox River.

632
00:37:46,510 --> 00:37:49,740
How some days you wished you'd never heard

633
00:37:49,780 --> 00:37:51,940
the name Michael Scofield.

634
00:37:53,910 --> 00:37:56,210
Even admitted to lying,

635
00:37:56,250 --> 00:37:58,380
keeping it all from me.

636
00:37:58,420 --> 00:38:01,500
How you finally came clean

637
00:38:01,580 --> 00:38:03,790
and put it all behind you?

638
00:38:05,490 --> 00:38:07,260
Sure.

639
00:38:07,290 --> 00:38:10,430
I forgave you for the lies.

640
00:38:10,460 --> 00:38:12,600
Your past.

641
00:38:12,630 --> 00:38:14,330
Accepted you.

642
00:38:14,370 --> 00:38:16,470
Loved you and Mike.

643
00:38:16,500 --> 00:38:18,500
How is that not enough for you?

644
00:38:35,550 --> 00:38:36,790
Hi.

645
00:38:36,820 --> 00:38:37,950
Hello?

646
00:38:37,990 --> 00:38:39,620
I have him.

647
00:38:39,660 --> 00:38:42,290
Thank God.

648
00:38:42,330 --> 00:38:43,890
He's fine.

649
00:38:43,930 --> 00:38:45,460
Headed home now.

650
00:38:45,500 --> 00:38:46,700
Hi, Mom.

651
00:38:46,730 --> 00:38:49,430
Oh, Heather, thank God.

652
00:38:49,470 --> 00:38:51,630
I'll be there soon.

653
00:39:34,580 --> 00:39:37,000
Navigation's been trashed,

654
00:39:37,040 --> 00:39:39,140
the controls damaged.

655
00:39:41,210 --> 00:39:42,480
Damn it.

656
00:39:42,510 --> 00:39:44,110
Tramp's off course.

657
00:39:44,150 --> 00:39:47,050
Moving toward Algerian waters, top speed.

658
00:39:47,080 --> 00:39:48,480
Can we fix it?

659
00:39:48,520 --> 00:39:49,550
It'll take time.

660
00:39:49,590 --> 00:39:50,700
And by then we'd be out

661
00:39:50,800 --> 00:39:51,940
of international waters.

662
00:39:52,390 --> 00:39:55,420
Falcon One requesting orders.

663
00:39:55,460 --> 00:39:58,430
We have a situation.

664
00:40:00,200 --> 00:40:01,630
Yeah.

665
00:40:01,660 --> 00:40:03,900
The SEAL team failed to neutralize Outis.

666
00:40:03,930 --> 00:40:06,260
Somehow the ship's controls were damaged.

667
00:40:06,340 --> 00:40:07,620
It's headed for Algerian waters

668
00:40:07,680 --> 00:40:09,340
with our soldiers on boards,

669
00:40:09,370 --> 00:40:10,900
but it'll cause a diplomatic incident

670
00:40:10,940 --> 00:40:13,240
if they stay to finish the job.

671
00:40:13,280 --> 00:40:15,710
The navy just made the call to pull the team.

672
00:40:15,740 --> 00:40:17,310
All right, all right.

673
00:40:17,350 --> 00:40:19,210
The SEALs couldn't do it. We escalate our move.

674
00:40:19,250 --> 00:40:21,150
Shouldn't have brought a knife to a gunfight.

675
00:40:21,180 --> 00:40:22,720
I will handle from here. Thank you.

676
00:40:36,770 --> 00:40:37,860
Sir.

677
00:40:37,900 --> 00:40:39,370
Yes.

678
00:40:39,400 --> 00:40:42,300
I have an ask, one that's imperative.

679
00:40:42,340 --> 00:40:45,510
I believe you'll find that our interests are aligned.

680
00:41:00,860 --> 00:41:02,260
What are they doing?

681
00:41:02,290 --> 00:41:03,260
They're leaving.

682
00:41:03,290 --> 00:41:04,590
Why?

683
00:41:04,630 --> 00:41:05,760
Run!

684
00:41:05,790 --> 00:41:08,860
Oh, God. No, no, no, no!

685
00:41:11,320 --> 00:41:13,130
Hey! You're gonna want this.

686
00:41:44,070 --> 00:41:47,230
Mike is safe where you can't touch him, and this is over.

687
00:41:48,340 --> 00:41:51,400
The life, the lies, the mask.

688
00:41:51,440 --> 00:41:54,140
You're gonna tell me everything.

689
00:41:54,180 --> 00:41:56,480
Like who you really are,

690
00:41:56,510 --> 00:41:59,580
what this was, all of it.

691
00:41:59,620 --> 00:42:03,480
It was our life.

692
00:42:03,520 --> 00:42:05,620
It's not over, Sara.

693
00:42:05,650 --> 00:42:08,390
Not even close.

694
00:42:08,420 --> 00:42:10,460
And Mike was never in danger.

695
00:42:10,540 --> 00:42:12,000
I love him.

696
00:42:12,460 --> 00:42:14,960
He is my family.

697
00:42:15,120 --> 00:42:17,200
I raised him.

698
00:42:17,280 --> 00:42:18,620
What have you done?

699
00:42:18,860 --> 00:42:23,740
No. It's what you've done, Sara.

700
00:42:23,770 --> 00:42:27,610
All of this could've been avoided.

701
00:42:29,510 --> 00:42:30,780
Good sleepover?

702
00:42:30,810 --> 00:42:31,810
Yeah.

703
00:42:31,850 --> 00:42:33,450
Is Mommy coming to pick me up?

704
00:42:33,480 --> 00:42:36,020
Yes, sir.

705
00:42:37,390 --> 00:42:40,390
Michael's dead.

706
00:42:40,420 --> 00:42:43,560
Your Nightingale trip to Greece led me straight to him.

707
00:42:45,030 --> 00:42:48,560
So... it's all on you, Sara.

708
00:42:48,600 --> 00:42:51,900
And your plan with Heather didn't work.

709
00:42:51,930 --> 00:42:54,170
Where's my son?

710
00:42:54,200 --> 00:42:55,300
I have him.

711
00:42:56,540 --> 00:42:58,210
And whether or not I have to threaten him...

712
00:42:58,240 --> 00:43:00,140
which I don't want to do...

713
00:43:00,180 --> 00:43:03,840
is entirely contingent upon you putting the gun down.

714
00:43:20,820 --> 00:43:56,900
m m 0 19 l 39 19 l 39 58 l 0 58

715
00:43:20,820 --> 00:43:56,900
m m 0 19 l 39 19 l 39 58 l 0 58

716
00:43:20,820 --> 00:43:56,900
m 32 27 l 32 27 l 32 29 l 31 29 l 31 28 l 30 28 l 30 29 l 29 29 l 29 30 l 28 30 l 28 31 l 27 31 l 27 32 l 26 32 l 26 33 l 28 33 l 28 32 l 30 32 l 30 33 l 28 33 l 28 34 l 27 34 l 27 36 l 26 36 l 26 37 l 25 37 l 25 36 l 24 36 l 24 33 l 22 33 l 22 32 l 23 32 l 23 31 l 22 31 l 22 30 l 24 30 l 24 31 l 26 31 l 26 30 l 24 30 l 24 28 l 23 28 l 23 29 l 22 29 l 22 30 l 21 30 l 21 31 l 19 31 l 19 32 l 20 32 l 20 33 l 19 33 l 19 32 l 18 32 l 18 33 l 17 33 l 17 32 l 18 32 l 18 31 l 17 31 l 17 30 l 19 30 l 19 29 l 19 29 l 20 29 l 20 30 l 21 30 l 21 29 l 20 29 l 20 28 l 22 28 l 22 27 l 27 27 l 27 28 l 25 28 l 25 29 l 28 29 l 28 25 l 27 25 l 27 26 l 26 26 l 26 25 l 27 25 l 27 24 l 28 24 l 28 23 l 27 23 l 27 22 l 29 22 l 29 27 l 32 27 m 16 29 l 17 29 l 17 28 l 16 28 l 16 29 m 17 26 l 16 26 l 16 25 l 17 25 l 17 26 m 18 29 l 18 27 l 19 27 l 19 26 l 20 26 l 20 25 l 19 25 l 19 26 l 18 26 l 18 25 l 19 25 l 19 24 l 20 24 l 20 22 l 21 22 l 21 21 l 22 21 l 22 24 l 20 24 l 20 25 l 21 25 l 21 27 l 20 27 l 20 28 l 19 28 l 19 29 l 18 29 m 23 26 l 22 26 l 22 25 l 23 25 l 23 26 m 24 26 l 24 24 l 23 24 l 23 21 l 24 21 l 24 22 l 26 22 l 26 24 l 25 24 l 25 26 m 0 28 l 0 30 l 1 30 l 1 29 l 2 29 l 2 30 l 3 30 l 3 33 l 2 33 l 2 34 l 1 34 l 1 33 l 0 33 l 0 34 l 1 34 l 1 35 l 2 35 l 2 37 l 1 37 l 1 36 l 0 36 l 0 38 l 2 38 l 2 39 l 5 39 l 5 40 l 7 40 l 7 39 l 6 39 l 6 38 l 8 38 l 8 37 l 9 37 l 9 36 l 10 36 l 10 37 l 11 37 l 11 36 l 10 36 l 10 34 l 9 34 l 9 36 l 8 36 l 8 34 l 9 34 l 9 33 l 6 33 l 6 32 l 5 32 l 5 31 l 6 31 l 6 32 l 8 32 l 8 31 l 6 31 l 6 30 l 8 30 l 8 28 l 7 28 l 7 29 l 6 29 l 6 30 l 4 30 l 4 28 l 5 28 l 5 29 l 6 29 l 6 28 l 7 28 l 7 27 l 6 27 l 6 28 l 5 28 l 5 27 l 2 27 l 2 28 l 3 28 l 3 29 l 2 29 l 2 28 l 1 28 m 0 31 l 2 31 l 2 32 l 0 32 m 9 31 l 10 31 l 10 32 l 9 32 l 9 31 m 21 32 l 22 32 l 22 31 l 21 31 l 21 32 m 37 27 l 34 27 l 34 28 l 33 28 l 33 29 l 32 29 l 32 30 l 31 30 l 31 29 l 30 29 l 30 32 l 31 32 l 31 33 l 30 33 l 30 34 l 29 34 l 29 36 l 28 36 l 28 37 l 26 37 l 26 40 l 25 40 l 25 41 l 24 41 l 24 39 l 23 39 l 23 41 l 24 41 l 24 43 l 22 43 l 22 42 l 19 42 l 19 43 l 20 43 l 20 44 l 21 44 l 21 45 l 19 45 l 19 46 l 22 46 l 22 44 l 25 44 l 25 41 l 26 41 l 26 44 l 27 44 l 27 42 l 28 42 l 28 44 l 30 44 l 30 45 l 32 45 l 32 46 l 33 46 l 33 45 l 34 45 l 34 44 l 35 44 l 35 43 l 33 43 l 33 45 l 32 45 l 32 44 l 32 42 l 31 42 l 31 43 l 30 43 l 30 42 l 29 42 l 29 41 l 26 41 l 26 40 l 27 40 l 27 38 l 28 38 l 28 39 l 29 39 l 29 41 l 30 41 l 30 42 l 31 42 l 31 41 l 32 41 l 32 40 l 34 40 l 34 41 l 34 42 l 36 42 l 36 44 l 37 44 l 37 43 l 37 40 l 36 40 l 36 41 l 35 41 l 35 39 l 36 39 l 36 38 l 37 38 l 37 37 l 35 37 l 35 35 l 34 35 l 34 36 l 33 36 l 33 37 l 35 37 l 35 39 l 33 39 l 33 37 l 32 37 l 32 38 l 30 38 l 30 39 l 29 39 l 29 38 l 28 38 l 28 37 l 30 37 l 30 36 l 31 36 l 31 37 l 32 37 l 32 36 l 33 36 l 33 34 l 34 34 l 34 33 l 35 33 l 35 34 l 36 34 l 36 35 l 37 35 l 37 33 l 35 33 l 35 31 l 32 31 l 32 30 l 33 30 l 33 29 l 35 29 l 35 28 l 37 28 l 37 27 m 33 32 l 33 33 l 32 33 l 32 32 m 31 34 l 32 34 l 32 35 l 31 35 m 25 35 l 26 35 l 26 34 l 25 34 m 36 29 l 36 29 l 37 29 l 37 30 l 36 30 m 36 31 l 37 31 l 37 32 l 36 32 m 14 36 l 14 34 l 13 34 l 13 35 l 12 35 l 12 38 l 13 38 l 13 36 m 4 38 l 4 37 l 3 37 l 3 38 l 2 38 l 2 37 l 3 37 l 3 33 l 5 33 l 5 34 l 4 34 l 4 35 l 6 35 l 6 34 l 7 34 l 7 35 l 6 35 l 6 36 l 7 36 l 7 37 l 6 37 l 6 38 l 4 38 m 4 36 l 5 36 l 5 37 l 4 37 m 37 46 l 37 45 l 36 45 l 36 44 l 35 44 l 35 45 l 34 45 l 34 46 l 35 46 l 35 47 l 34 47 l 34 48 l 35 48 l 35 51 l 34 51 l 34 53 l 33 53 l 33 55 l 31 55 l 31 54 l 32 54 l 32 53 l 33 53 l 33 50 l 34 50 l 34 49 l 33 49 l 33 47 l 29 47 l 29 46 l 28 46 l 28 47 l 27 47 l 27 46 l 28 46 l 28 45 l 26 45 l 26 47 l 25 47 l 25 48 l 24 48 l 24 46 l 25 46 l 25 45 l 23 45 l 23 47 l 21 47 l 21 48 l 20 48 l 20 47 l 19 47 l 19 50 l 21 50 l 21 53 l 19 53 l 19 54 l 21 54 l 21 56 l 23 56 l 23 55 l 22 55 l 22 54 l 23 54 l 23 53 l 22 53 l 22 52 l 24 52 l 24 53 l 25 53 l 25 52 l 26 52 l 26 51 l 25 51 l 25 50 l 24 50 l 24 51 l 22 51 l 22 50 l 23 50 l 23 49 l 26 49 l 26 48 l 28 48 l 28 49 l 28 49 l 26 49 l 26 51 l 27 51 l 27 50 l 28 50 l 28 51 l 27 51 l 27 52 l 28 52 l 28 54 l 27 54 l 27 53 l 26 53 l 26 56 l 28 56 l 28 55 l 29 55 l 29 52 l 30 52 l 30 53 l 31 53 l 31 52 l 32 52 l 32 53 l 31 53 l 31 54 l 30 54 l 30 55 l 29 55 l 29 56 l 37 56 l 37 53 l 36 53 l 36 55 l 34 55 l 34 54 l 35 54 l 35 51 l 37 51 l 37 49 l 36 49 l 36 46 m 29 48 l 32 48 l 32 51 l 29 51 m 30 49 l 31 49 l 31 50 l 30 50 m 13 50 l 15 50 l 15 47 l 16 47 l 16 46 l 17 46 l 17 45 l 18 45 l 18 43 l 17 43 l 17 42 l 14 42 l 14 43 l 16 43 l 16 46 l 15 46 l 15 44 l 14 44 l 14 43 l 13 43 l 13 45 l 11 45 l 11 44 l 12 44 l 12 43 l 9 43 l 9 45 l 8 45 l 8 43 l 6 43 l 6 42 l 10 42 l 10 40 l 11 40 l 11 42 l 13 42 l 13 41 l 14 41 l 14 40 l 13 40 l 13 41 l 12 41 l 12 40 l 11 40 l 11 38 l 9 38 l 9 39 l 8 39 l 8 41 l 5 41 l 5 42 l 3 42 l 3 41 l 0 41 l 0 43 l 1 43 l 1 42 l 2 42 l 2 44 l 0 44 l 0 48 l 1 48 l 1 45 l 2 45 l 2 47 l 3 47 l 3 45 l 2 45 l 2 44 l 3 44 l 3 43 l 4 43 l 4 48 l 5 48 l 5 47 l 6 47 l 6 46 l 7 46 l 7 45 l 6 45 l 6 44 l 5 44 l 5 43 l 6 43 l 6 44 l 7 44 l 7 45 l 8 45 l 8 47 l 6 47 l 6 48 l 8 48 l 8 49 l 9 49 l 9 46 l 10 46 l 10 45 l 11 45 l 11 46 l 10 46 l 10 47 l 11 47 l 11 48 l 10 48 l 10 49 l 11 49 l 11 48 l 14 48 l 14 49 l 13 49 m 13 47 l 12 47 l 12 46 l 13 46 m 15 56 l 11 56 l 11 55 l 9 55 l 9 54 l 8 54 l 8 51 l 9 51 l 9 53 l 10 53 l 10 50 l 11 50 l 11 54 l 12 54 l 12 52 l 13 52 l 13 51 l 14 51 l 14 52 l 13 52 l 13 54 l 12 54 l 12 55 l 15 55 l 15 55 m 15 54 l 15 53 l 17 53 l 17 54 l 18 54 l 18 56 l 16 56 l 16 54 m 17 48 l 18 48 l 18 50 l 16 50 l 16 49 l 17 49 m 17 51 l 18 51 l 18 52 l 17 52 m 19 51 l 20 51 l 20 52 l 19 52 m 19 55 l 20 55 l 20 56 l 19 56 m 0 39 l 1 39 l 1 40 l 0 40 m 0 49 l 7 49 l 7 56 l 0 56 l 0 56 m 1 50 l 1 55 l 1 55 l 6 55 l 6 50 m 2 51 l 5 51 l 5 54 l 2 54 m 30 19 l 30 26 l 37 26 l 37 19 m 31 20 l 36 20 l 36 25 l 31 25 m 32 21 l 32 24 l 35 24 l 35 21 m 0 19 l 7 19 l 7 26 l 0 26 m 1 20 l 1 25 l 6 25 l 6 20 m 2 21 l 2 24 l 5 24 l 5 21 m 8 19 l 8 22 l 11 22 l 11 23 l 10 23 l 10 24 l 8 24 l 8 28 l 10 28 l 10 29 l 12 29 l 12 33 l 10 33 l 10 34 l 11 34 l 11 35 l 12 35 l 12 34 l 13 34 l 13 33 l 15 33 l 15 32 l 16 32 l 16 30 l 15 30 l 15 31 l 14 31 l 14 30 l 15 30 l 15 29 l 14 29 l 14 28 l 13 28 l 13 24 l 15 24 l 15 25 l 14 25 l 14 27 l 15 27 l 15 28 l 16 28 l 16 26 l 15 26 l 15 25 l 16 25 l 16 24 l 17 24 l 17 25 l 18 25 l 18 23 l 19 23 l 19 21 l 21 21 l 21 20 l 23 20 l 23 19 l 21 19 l 21 20 l 19 20 l 19 19 l 18 19 l 18 21 l 17 21 l 17 23 l 15 23 l 15 22 l 16 22 l 16 21 l 17 21 l 17 20 l 16 20 l 16 21 l 15 21 l 15 20 l 16 20 l 16 19 l 14 19 l 14 21 l 15 21 l 15 22 l 14 22 l 14 21 l 13 21 l 13 22 l 12 22 l 12 20 l 13 20 l 13 19 l 11 19 l 11 20 l 9 20 l 9 19 m 9 27 l 9 25 l 10 25 l 10 24 l 11 24 l 11 23 l 12 23 l 12 28 l 11 28 l 11 27 m 10 26 l 10 25 l 11 25 l 11 26 m 25 19 l 25 20 l 26 20 l 26 19 m 28 19 l 29 19 l 29 21 l 27 21 l 27 20 l 28 20

717
00:43:20,820 --> 00:43:56,900
m 56 35 l 43 41 l 52 41 l 52 39 l 56 39 m 73 28 l 77 41 l 82 41 m 69 21 l 61 21 l 64 23 l 64 39 l 63 41 l 70 41 l 65 28 l 67 23 l 71 23 m 25 28 l 17 41 l 33 41 m 31 21 l 52 21 l 42 25 l 42 29 l 53 24 l 55 26 l 42 32 l 42 35 l 56 29 l 56 31 l 42 37 l 41 39 m 29 9 l 55 9 l 55 11 l 41 11 l 41 17 l 51 17 l 51 14 l 65 14 l 68 18 l 29 18 m 20 11 l 16 18 l 20 18 m 14 21 l 19 21 l 8 39 l 7 39 l 7 41 l 1 41

