[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.1
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Default Aegisub file
ScriptType: v4.00+
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: yes
YCbCr Matrix: None

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: OL,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,95,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,1
Style: 宣传信息,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.2,0.2,9,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组,微软雅黑,35,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,70,100,6,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 二维码,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 声明,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HC85A5A5A,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 音乐,方正兰亭特黑简体,20,&H000EDDE5,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 大家字幕组1,微软雅黑,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0.5,0.5,2,5,5,2,134
Style: Bosch片头,经典综艺体简,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HE6E28609,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: Bosch歌词,方正字迹-杜慧田硬笔楷书,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&HDC0B9016,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: Bosch职员,经典综艺体简,18,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,5,10,10,10,1
Style: BoschS3E10特效,苹方 中等,16,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,1,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.41,0:00:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Don't you have a job or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.70,0:00:04.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, on a freelance cargo ship.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.99,0:00:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We go to Hong Kong, Spain,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.80,0:00:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Buenos Aires, basically wherever the boss tells us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.84,0:00:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Corrupt son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.47,0:00:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We've awoken something, something people are trying to
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.36,0:00:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}hide about Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.44,0:00:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who the hell is this Poseidon guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.97,0:00:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A psychopath.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.34,0:00:18.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A frustrated policy wonk
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.11,0:00:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}in the CIA who created a cell
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.21,0:00:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}within the CIA called 21-Void.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.31,0:00:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And they needed my help
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.85,0:00:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}breaking out people in prison
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.08,0:00:27.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}all over the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.85,0:00:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Before he was killed,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.15,0:00:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Kellerman had been looking into 21-Void.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.89,0:00:32.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I need you to look into the possibility
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.16,0:00:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that there was an insider involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.56,0:00:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I wasn't expecting a call at this hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.29,0:00:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think we need to meet soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.59,0:00:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was looking for where the man went.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.40,0:00:40.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What man, baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.46,0:00:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The man that gave me this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.73,0:00:42.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.90,0:00:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What are you into?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.17,0:00:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Just tell us where you're headed.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.74,0:00:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}300 miles across the desert, Phaeacia.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.21,0:00:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Autonomous zone. No ISIL.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.17,0:00:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can lead you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.38,0:00:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Phaeacia, we found it!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.26,0:01:10.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Back in the city, I told you you would die.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.99,0:01:12.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.06,0:01:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He poisoned me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.65,0:01:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's incredible how good you've gotten at drawing, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.26,0:01:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Really, that's...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.93,0:01:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that's so good.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.86,0:01:48.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's a Greek hero.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.26,0:01:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He looks hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.90,0:01:52.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They all get hurt sooner or later.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.34,0:01:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's what's great about Greek heroes,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.20,0:01:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}they're real, not supermen.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.31,0:02:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They get hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.24,0:02:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They can die.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.92,0:02:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, I'm sorry, buddy, last little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.06,0:02:15.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got to keep it clean, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.09,0:02:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's looking much better though, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.76,0:02:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're doing good. You just hang in there, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.56,0:02:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How we doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.83,0:02:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Got something.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Our friend over there has a boat.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.26,0:02:26.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's making a smuggling run to Greece.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.44,0:02:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He says he can take your brother to a first world doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.41,0:02:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}First world thinks he's Kaniel Outis.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.61,0:02:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They'll arrest him on sight.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.14,0:02:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.61,0:02:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's the alternative, let him die?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.95,0:02:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What kind of a brother are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.88,0:02:41.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You say something like that again,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.18,0:02:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I swear to God, I'll kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.56,0:02:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There might be a third option.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.37,0:03:02.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So how was your first day back?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.17,0:03:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have to say, it's never been so rewarding
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.64,0:03:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to teach game theory to the tops
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.88,0:03:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}of a bunch of 18-year-olds' heads
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.31,0:03:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}while they're busy sexting each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.48,0:03:14.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.92,0:03:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}normalcy's threatening to come back,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.52,0:03:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I say cheers to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.76,0:03:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Cheers to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.79,0:03:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on, let's sit outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.16,0:03:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll be right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.17,0:03:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.47,0:03:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We found Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.67,0:03:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is he our Michael?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.17,0:03:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yes, Sara.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.76,0:03:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sara, listen, he's been poisoned.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.70,0:03:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We think it's antifreeze.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.93,0:03:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's lost a lot of blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.20,0:03:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He needs a lot of blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.54,0:03:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.97,0:03:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He needs a lot of things if it's antifreeze.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.57,0:03:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Listen, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.84,0:03:56.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}we're heading to Greece.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.54,0:03:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is there any way we can get some medical help off the books?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.78,0:04:00.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, no, no, no, no, this isn't the kind of thing
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.41,0:04:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that you want to do off the books.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.98,0:04:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Listen, Lincoln, he's gonna need a transfusion.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.18,0:04:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael's B negative, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.92,0:04:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's maybe one percent of the population with that blood type.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.96,0:04:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You won't find it where you're going,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.72,0:04:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and he won't make it while you look.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.96,0:04:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Unless it comes to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.13,0:04:20.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.20,0:04:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.44,0:04:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.04,0:04:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.94,0:04:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You got to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.88,0:04:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}‭Go where?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.31,0:04:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}To Crete.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.85,0:04:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael, um,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.28,0:04:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}they found him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.92,0:04:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.35,0:04:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's poisoned.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.59,0:04:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael? Your ex, Michael?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.99,0:04:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.32,0:04:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Wait, hold on a second,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.49,0:04:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}he really is alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.89,0:04:48.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He contacted you just now?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.43,0:04:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, and, uh, and he needs help,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.90,0:04:55.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I think I'm the only one that can help him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.58,0:05:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}yeah, I can get there faster on a plane than they can on a boat.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.81,0:05:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Whoa, whoa, whoa, Sara?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.44,0:05:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Y-You don't owe him that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.31,0:05:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You don't know what you'd be walking into. It's not safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.28,0:05:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll be fine. I don't have a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.68,0:05:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.02,0:05:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This has been a hell of a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.22,0:05:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, look, I know you've got a million questions,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.16,0:05:17.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}just like I do, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.02,0:05:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't look my son in the eye
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.56,0:05:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and tell him that I let his father die
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.66,0:05:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}when I could've tried to save him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.00,0:05:26.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A father he's never met.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.37,0:05:28.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.97,0:05:30.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And if I told you not to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.47,0:05:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}"If's" A big word in that sentence.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.14,0:05:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Jacob, are you telling me not to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.61,0:05:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.18,0:05:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.18,0:05:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.26,0:06:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Should've left her out of this, Linc.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.83,0:06:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shut up. You're about to see the wife you haven't seen
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.40,0:06:05.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}in seven years.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.97,0:06:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- I got you, I got you. - Cast off.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.91,0:06:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.74,0:06:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.65,0:06:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Been locked up for longer than I can remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.45,0:06:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Before Ogygia, it was my apartment, my head
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.42,0:06:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and my phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.49,0:06:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Walls all around me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.02,0:06:27.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Couldn't see the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.86,0:06:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I like it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.40,0:06:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No walls.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.83,0:06:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Freedom, like I haven't had in a long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.40,0:06:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can start over.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.11,0:06:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And unless you say you need me,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.11,0:06:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'd like to stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.08,0:06:46.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're a free man, Ja.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.61,0:06:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The choice is yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.72,0:06:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I owe you my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.62,0:06:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You gave me back the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.12,0:06:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Get him healthy. Get safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.96,0:07:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.03,0:07:03.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}See you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.40,0:07:08.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, hey, hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.63,0:07:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got to know,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.10,0:07:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you really got Freddie Mercury's ashes?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.54,0:07:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is it true Keith Richards snorted his dead father's ashes?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.31,0:07:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.91,0:07:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.15,0:07:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Keep alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.95,0:07:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You too, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.33,0:07:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Linc,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.76,0:07:38.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}how far is it to Greece?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.60,0:07:40.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}12 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.67,0:07:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sara's gonna be there in 12.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.27,0:07:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't think I have 12 hours in me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.46,0:09:06.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was right, we got problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.94,0:09:11.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Apparently, State Department is asking questions about 21-Void
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.04,0:09:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}after our visit to NSA yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.41,0:09:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They have no viable information.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.41,0:09:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}21-Void doesn't exist.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.48,0:09:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Poseidon will clean house.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.92,0:09:22.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The problem's not going away.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.09,0:09:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That State Department agent wants to meet
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.32,0:09:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}as soon as we land.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.47,0:09:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Chania, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.77,0:09:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.49,0:09:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It is safe here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.29,0:09:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I use when I come.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.86,0:10:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You got any food for him?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.49,0:10:02.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come, it's in the boat.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.69,0:10:05.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Great, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.30,0:10:07.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Keep his spirits up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.03,0:10:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All right, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.97,0:10:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.91,0:10:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Got to hang in there, buddy, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.45,0:10:28.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Still got a lot of things to tell me, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.46,0:10:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You gonna tell me why I'm your whip hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.39,0:10:35.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.73,0:10:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got a lot invested in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.31,0:10:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can't die on me now, Michael, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.51,0:10:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Called you Michael.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.31,0:10:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The first... first time I ever really known your name,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.98,0:11:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}even though I feel like...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.39,0:11:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I feel like we've been brothers since we met, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.90,0:11:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know, with... with Linc here...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.90,0:11:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}...it was the first time I ever felt like an outsider with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.94,0:11:23.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know, like...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.14,0:11:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}like I lost...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.98,0:11:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}part of my family or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.85,0:11:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, you see, Michael, you can't die.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.12,0:11:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Please?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.41,0:12:32.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Linc.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.34,0:13:00.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I missed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.88,0:13:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm gonna fix you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.65,0:13:14.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And then we'll talk, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.12,0:13:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm gonna make you okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.63,0:13:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.56,0:13:26.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}shh, shh, shh, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.03,0:13:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, Lincoln, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.07,0:13:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}would you pass me that coatrack?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.04,0:13:34.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Could I grab the chair, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.84,0:13:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.20,0:14:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We'll do a transfusion.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.70,0:14:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm O negative.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.94,0:14:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's the universal donor.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.54,0:14:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Turns out it's the only other blood type I could've given him.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.04,0:14:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe there's something to destiny, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.18,0:14:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is he gonna live?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.22,0:14:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.92,0:14:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, he'll live.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.23,0:14:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Give him a couple hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.86,0:14:33.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.50,0:14:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We'll, uh... we'll give you a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.84,0:14:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.77,0:14:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.98,0:14:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.75,0:14:54.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We need to work out a way to get off this island.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.96,0:15:03.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What I said...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.63,0:15:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}um, about you...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.30,0:15:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.37,0:15:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A man would be lucky to have a brother
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.84,0:15:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}cares as much as you, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.78,0:15:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Wife like that...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.51,0:15:24.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}...family.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.65,0:15:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I wouldn't call it luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.75,0:15:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You've been through what we've been through.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.49,0:15:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're family now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.86,0:15:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll drink to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.26,0:15:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.07,0:15:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Flying's really out of the question?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.70,0:15:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.87,0:15:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Airports are worse than hospitals.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.81,0:15:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And once the name Kaniel Outis is radioactive,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.84,0:15:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}they'll shoot him on sight.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.18,0:15:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So another boat?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.55,0:16:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Across the Atlantic?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.58,0:16:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mm, I'm no sailor, but I know that no boat in that harbor
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.82,0:16:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}is gonna get us that far.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.33,0:16:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We need a big boat.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.50,0:16:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}One that doesn't mind a radioactive cargo, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.31,0:16:34.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey there, I wanted to follow up on our conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.05,0:16:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Obviously, the CIA and State,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.79,0:16:37.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}we've been sharing information on Kaniel Outis,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.82,0:16:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but my question for you is:
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.06,0:16:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Outis killed Abu Ramal,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.76,0:16:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}did the country a service.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.16,0:16:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So why were you still at NSA yesterday,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.80,0:16:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}trying to kill him?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.83,0:16:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why don't we get off the tarmac?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.87,0:16:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We'll share what we can about our investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.54,0:16:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This is all just bureaucratic miscommunication.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.27,0:16:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We can iron it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.51,0:17:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So you know, we checked with CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.88,0:17:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The CIA didn't sanction your visit to NSA yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.18,0:17:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No one even knew you were there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.98,0:17:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who are you working for, really?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.52,0:17:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And why were you trying to take out Kaniel Outis?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.63,0:17:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Never thought I'd see this face again.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.13,0:17:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You weren't supposed to.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.20,0:17:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.91,0:17:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll tell you everything you want to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.38,0:17:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But first, I need something from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.91,0:17:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.38,0:17:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A picture of my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.46,0:17:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We weren't at NSA yesterday.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.33,0:17:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm telling you, this is a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.56,0:17:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And it's a mistake to lie to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.20,0:17:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can have you prosecuted.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.96,0:17:57.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have a contact at the NSA and she gave me proof.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.90,0:18:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're not calling him Junior, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.67,0:18:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I promised you I would never do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.04,0:18:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's an amazing kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.61,0:18:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.19,0:18:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.10,0:18:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.28,0:18:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.55,0:18:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Jacob?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.65,0:18:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Jacob.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.19,0:18:56.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Jacob is Poseidon.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.40,0:19:06.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I knewt. I wasn't crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.63,0:19:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I caught him lying, but he-he--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.14,0:19:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}oh, God, he covered it so well.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.77,0:19:14.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He was... honest and hurt,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.81,0:19:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and I bought it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.44,0:19:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.88,0:19:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.65,0:19:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's a CIA operative, deep cover.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.12,0:19:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He runs a splinter cell called 21-Void.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.38,0:19:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What does this have to do with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.75,0:19:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He targeted me for my skills,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.49,0:19:31.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}blackmailed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.06,0:19:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He told me if I didn't agree to come work for him,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.53,0:19:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}he'd go after you and Linc,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.33,0:19:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}put you both in jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.25,0:19:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And then he proved it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.39,0:19:45.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He said I could never see either one of you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.73,0:19:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Or Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.62,0:19:50.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Made me fake my death.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.66,0:19:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And then he just used me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.30,0:19:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He married me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.83,0:19:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If I'd known he was your husband, I swear...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.67,0:19:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, no, no, no, no,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.77,0:19:59.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}this is not on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.80,0:20:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.64,0:20:05.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why now? Why did you come back now?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.01,0:20:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The origami...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.88,0:20:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Four years ago, he betrayed me
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.65,0:20:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and now I know why.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.28,0:20:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He wanted me out of the way...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.79,0:20:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}so he could have you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.49,0:20:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How did he betray you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.89,0:20:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He set a meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.16,0:20:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We were supposed to discuss my next assignment.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.06,0:20:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What he didn't tell me was that
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.70,0:20:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}we were meeting a man named Harlan Gaines,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.17,0:20:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}a deputy director of the CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.07,0:20:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Gaines was investigating 21-Void.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.27,0:20:40.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Looking for the traitor behind it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.58,0:20:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's when I knew my work wasn't sanctioned by the CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.71,0:20:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Poseidon shot and killed Gaines that night,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.95,0:20:49.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to stop the investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.56,0:20:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He told me to move the body,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.96,0:20:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}make it look like it never happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.39,0:20:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I've seen the photos of that part, they're damning.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.66,0:21:02.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He chose images that showed me moving Gaines' body,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.40,0:21:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}eliminated the ones that incriminated himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.57,0:21:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I knew I was being set up.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.64,0:21:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He was tightening his control over me,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.57,0:21:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but there was nothing I could do.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.94,0:21:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}At least, that's what he thought.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.91,0:21:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}When I knew Poseidon had gone rogue
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.72,0:21:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and was operating outside the CIA,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.18,0:21:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that's when I started my plan to get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.62,0:21:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.99,0:21:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Some other man has your--
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.99,0:21:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}your face, your past, your whole life.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.86,0:21:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sara, there is a plan to make this right,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.63,0:21:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}to protect our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.50,0:21:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael, he's with our son right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.30,0:21:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's with Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.57,0:21:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I, uh, look, I have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.18,0:21:52.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, Noah, you gonna build us a boat?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.08,0:21:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Nope. I'm gonna do one better.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.82,0:21:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who you calling?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.52,0:22:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A friend who actually has a boat.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.20,0:22:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.70,0:22:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sucre, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.90,0:22:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Linc? I thought the Middle East
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.94,0:22:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}was gonna swallow you up, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.21,0:22:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where's Michael? Did you find him?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.11,0:22:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Listen, that's why I'm calling.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.18,0:22:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We're on the island of Crete.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.85,0:22:25.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We need a low profile ride back to the States.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.78,0:22:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I would love to help,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.45,0:22:29.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but we're on the other side of the world, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.25,0:22:30.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We just dropped a load in Morocco.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.92,0:22:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What are you talking about? Morocco's near Crete.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.42,0:22:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, I know, of course it is,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.29,0:22:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but what I mean is it's not my ship.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.53,0:22:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, but what would it cost to hitch a ride?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.36,0:22:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can't hitch a ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.07,0:22:44.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You have to rent the whole ship.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.80,0:22:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The boss charges 50K a leg, Linc.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.24,0:22:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You want to get back to the States, it's 50K.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.47,0:22:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}50k?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.71,0:22:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We're just trying to get home.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.01,0:22:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know we don't have that kind of cash.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.65,0:22:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You do now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.31,0:23:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Here, this was my grandmother's.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.85,0:23:02.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's an heirloom worth at least that.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.49,0:23:08.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't think of a better use for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.69,0:23:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.49,0:23:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We got it, Sucre. Get to Crete.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.57,0:23:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's not gonna hurt Mike,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.82,0:23:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}not unless he suspects you know who he really is.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.54,0:23:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you remove his mask,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.01,0:23:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}he'll lash out.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.67,0:23:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know him better than I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.44,0:23:29.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's the point, no one knows him.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.21,0:23:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So, what do I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.01,0:23:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You play his game. You wear your own mask.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.65,0:23:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}As soon as you get a chance to get away with Mike,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.69,0:23:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you take it, disappear.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.32,0:23:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll get to the States as soon as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.52,0:23:45.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll find you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.23,0:23:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're looking better.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.00,0:23:48.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A little grayer, but better.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.83,0:23:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have an amazing doctor on call.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.67,0:24:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will wear the mask.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.64,0:24:04.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will play his game...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.18,0:24:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and if he hurts our son I'll kill him.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.75,0:24:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.44,0:24:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Please come back to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.69,0:24:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}She's leaving Crete alone,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.69,0:24:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}which means she left Outis behind, and he'll try to follow,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.93,0:24:56.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}return to the U.S. In the next day or two.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.70,0:24:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Who called? It can only be by ship or plane, so plaster his face
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.69,0:25:01.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}on all maritime and air channels,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.95,0:25:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}focusing on all vessels departing from Crete
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.64,0:25:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}in the next 48 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.71,0:25:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's got to be on one.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.48,0:25:08.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He can't make it back inside the country. Jacob?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.85,0:25:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Was that Mommy?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.18,0:25:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yes. Mommy's on her way home.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.55,0:25:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael Scofield.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.89,0:25:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My man, you got more lives than anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.79,0:25:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Think I might've used them all up.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.29,0:25:40.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A damn phoenix.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.93,0:25:42.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I can't believe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.56,0:25:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I want to hear every damn thing
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.13,0:25:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}that's happened to you since you died.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.87,0:25:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Papi, you're alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.67,0:25:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The skipper is a corrupt bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.21,0:25:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Don't mess with him. He's got guns in the hold,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.81,0:25:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- all kinds of contraband. - Captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.05,0:26:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Here's the cargo I was telling you about.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.88,0:26:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Pay up.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.75,0:26:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where's the 50K?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.95,0:26:06.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.72,0:26:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I said cash.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.62,0:26:11.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's a sapphire, six carats,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.96,0:26:15.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}flawless, surrounded by 2.5 carats of bezeled diamonds.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.60,0:26:17.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Street value is 125K.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.53,0:26:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You can pawn it for half that and still make a profit.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.21,0:26:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If it's fake,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.41,0:26:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}you go under the sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.42,0:26:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A boat is the last place I expected to find you, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.39,0:26:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I thought you hated the water.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.99,0:26:44.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, you remember, but I got a record.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.26,0:26:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Not a lot of employers lined up to take a chance on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.93,0:26:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Besides, this ship provides opportunities
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.36,0:26:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}for my side business...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.10,0:26:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}which is the real reason I'm on this boat.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.07,0:26:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This baby...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.04,0:26:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}houses my entire life savings.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.20,0:26:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm telling you, it's gonna be huge.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.57,0:27:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm a few months away from putting all this behind me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.28,0:27:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}If you guys are lucky, I'll let you guys
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.55,0:27:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}take one of my ladies for a spin.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.48,0:27:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.82,0:27:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What, sex dolls?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.85,0:27:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No, have some class, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.09,0:27:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The term is inflatables, high quality,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.89,0:27:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}expensive, very lifelike.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.69,0:27:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.68,0:27:41.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.92,0:27:44.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.00,0:28:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where's Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.30,0:28:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.70,0:28:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Kid had a big day.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.37,0:28:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Most important, though,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.58,0:28:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}how's Michael?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.11,0:28:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Were you able to help him?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.21,0:28:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I mean, he was barely alive when I got there.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.75,0:28:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He, uh, slept most of the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.42,0:28:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I... I did what I could for him. I, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.36,0:28:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I stabilized him, but he's changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.33,0:28:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He, uh... he's just not the guy I knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.63,0:28:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hmm. ‭So, they dropped me at the airport and that was that.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.57,0:28:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.67,0:28:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Linc and some other guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.08,0:28:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.78,0:28:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where's Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.35,0:28:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You said that he was asleep. ‭He is...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.19,0:28:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}at a friend's house, a sleepover.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.72,0:28:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay. Which friend?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.59,0:28:59.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's at Patrick's house.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.53,0:29:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What happened to your grandmother's ring?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.77,0:29:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm such an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.20,0:29:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I took it off on the way over for safekeeping,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.10,0:29:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}cause I didn't want it to get stolen,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.07,0:29:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}then when I looked for it on the way back it was gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.68,0:29:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Screamed so loud they nearly threw me off the flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.34,0:29:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.81,0:29:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We spoke to our man at the Pentagon.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.38,0:29:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}A naval alert just went out.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.98,0:29:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Kaniel Outis has been located
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.12,0:30:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}on a cargo ship in the Mediterranean.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.72,0:30:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It was reported by the ship's captain.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.69,0:30:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's the navy gonna do about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.36,0:30:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The nearest LCS combat craft
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.46,0:30:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}is moving to engage.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.30,0:30:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}SEAL team's been deployed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.86,0:30:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Orders?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.47,0:30:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}To seek and destroy Kaniel Outis.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.90,0:30:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.34,0:30:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We've done our job getting the message out.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.11,0:30:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Now it's time for the SEALs to do theirs.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.21,0:30:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}My God.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.15,0:30:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You've been through hell, my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.52,0:30:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Have some faith, papi.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.29,0:30:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thanks, papi.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.32,0:30:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What about you, Linc?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.76,0:30:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I think Linc's got a secret girlfriend,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.79,0:30:42.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the pilot lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.80,0:30:44.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}She's not my lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.16,0:30:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe Sucre will set you up with one of his sex dolls.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.73,0:30:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're not dolls, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.07,0:30:49.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, sorry, inflatables.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.60,0:30:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look, let's just change the subject, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.30,0:30:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You know, might be something to be said for settling down.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.07,0:30:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Right, well... that's not in the cards.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.88,0:31:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's locked from the outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.92,0:31:06.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They made you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.99,0:31:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You really are a wanted terrorist.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.99,0:31:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What did the hell did you think he was saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.22,0:31:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I thought it was an analogy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.19,0:31:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, for God's sake.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.46,0:31:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There's no other way
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.89,0:31:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}out of this cabin.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.83,0:31:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All crew to the top deck. All hands up.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.57,0:31:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Comply or be fired on.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.04,0:31:30.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}This ship is now under the control of the U.S. Navy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.91,0:31:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Prepared to be boarded.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.81,0:31:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We got company.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.48,0:31:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I say we jump.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.75,0:31:35.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's a long way down.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.92,0:31:37.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's the only way out.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.13,0:31:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's too far.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.98,0:31:39.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have an idea...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.32,0:31:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}...but it's gonna hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.40,0:32:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.34,0:32:06.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey, Heather, it's me. Listen, I can't talk,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.17,0:32:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but I need you to go pick up Mike right now, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.38,0:32:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you know where Patrick Monroe lives?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.84,0:32:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.84,0:32:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.05,0:32:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Listen, I'll explain later.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.58,0:32:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Don't bring him back here, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.45,0:32:17.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Keep him with you. I'll be over as soon as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.58,0:32:18.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Can you do that for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.92,0:32:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Uh, yeah. Uh, I'll leave right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.19,0:32:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I-I-Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.56,0:32:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.03,0:32:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.84,0:32:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Six. The rest with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.04,0:32:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.45,0:32:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}One, two, three, four.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.69,0:32:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Go, go.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.70,0:33:04.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll go left, you right.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.34,0:33:14.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They went out the window!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.41,0:33:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They went out the window!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.71,0:33:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What do you see?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.01,0:33:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No visual.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.81,0:33:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Alpha One, Alpha Two to portside, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.88,0:33:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.32,0:33:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.72,0:33:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Take... Take it off!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.43,0:33:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.46,0:33:35.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Fernando.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.30,0:33:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Fernando Sucre.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.90,0:33:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm a member of this crew. Check the roster, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.03,0:33:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I got no part in any of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.87,0:33:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Check the roster for Fernando Sucre.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.21,0:33:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Suspect seems to check out.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.93,0:33:50.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Take him to the bridge.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.41,0:33:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.08,0:33:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Let's move.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.49,0:34:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Absolutely no one gets off this ship, understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.95,0:34:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.94,0:34:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I don't know any Kaniel Outis.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.67,0:34:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The guy's name is Scofield.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.94,0:34:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Haven't seen him in years.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.21,0:34:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He calls me, he says he needs a ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.24,0:34:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We got active pursuit on engine deck.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.21,0:34:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Watch him.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.38,0:34:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The guy's name is Scofield!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.52,0:34:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That's the door Sucre told us about.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.16,0:34:38.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}There they are!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.56,0:34:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Freeze! Freeze!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.76,0:34:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Look alive
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.70,0:34:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We've got them bottled up.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.73,0:34:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Guys, come on! Hurry!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.53,0:34:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hurry!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.64,0:34:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's stuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.80,0:34:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}- Come on! - ‭It's stuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.24,0:34:54.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's stuck!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.34,0:34:55.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Smoke them out, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.09,0:35:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tear gas.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.62,0:35:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That hits the ventilation, it's gonna ruin my cargo.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.16,0:35:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You've always been a loser, Sucre.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.30,0:35:19.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Worst shipmate I ever hired.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.63,0:35:21.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You brought this scum on board my ship.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.30,0:35:23.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're your friends. Where are they going?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.14,0:35:24.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're associates of associates.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.27,0:35:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I haven't seen them in years.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.17,0:35:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}But that's a good point.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.51,0:35:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why don't you tell the nice SEAL here
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.04,0:35:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}how you accepted payment for their passage?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.15,0:35:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Maybe they're your friends, not mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.82,0:35:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Okay, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.02,0:35:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I heard them say something about container 17.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.50,0:35:54.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}That container 17.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.87,0:35:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The one with your super secret cargo, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.74,0:36:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Weapons and munitions?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.24,0:36:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Vincent, tangos may be arming themselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.48,0:36:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Man, they're not gonna like you if they find that, are they?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.41,0:36:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Vincent.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.11,0:36:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You might just end up on the terrorist watch list, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.75,0:36:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Vincent, do you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.75,0:36:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Can't read you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.69,0:36:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Good-for-nothing Mexican. You planned this.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.56,0:36:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.57,0:36:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}17's still sealed.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.41,0:36:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Captain?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.81,0:36:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'm Puerto Rican.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.35,0:36:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}twelve o' clock ,You hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.86,0:36:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.75,0:37:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Go, go. Move!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.68,0:37:08.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.02,0:37:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The ship's changing course.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.20,0:37:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I did it, papi.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.86,0:37:14.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No going back now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.71,0:37:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}See what their next move is.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.42,0:37:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Do you remember our honeymoon?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.93,0:37:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.77,0:37:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How you opened up.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.73,0:37:46.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Told me you carried shame for what you did at Fox River.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.51,0:37:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How some days you wished you'd never heard
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.78,0:37:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the name Michael Scofield.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.91,0:37:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Even admitted to lying,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.25,0:37:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}keeping it all from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.42,0:38:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How you finally came clean
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.58,0:38:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}and put it all behind you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.49,0:38:07.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.29,0:38:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I forgave you for the lies.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.46,0:38:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your past.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.63,0:38:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Accepted you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.37,0:38:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Loved you and Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.50,0:38:18.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}How is that not enough for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.55,0:38:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.82,0:38:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.99,0:38:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have him.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.66,0:38:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.33,0:38:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.93,0:38:45.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Headed home now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.50,0:38:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hi, Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.73,0:38:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, Heather, thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.47,0:38:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I'll be there soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.58,0:39:37.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Navigation's been trashed,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.04,0:39:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}the controls damaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.21,0:39:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.51,0:39:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Tramp's off course.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.15,0:39:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Moving toward Algerian waters, top speed.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.08,0:39:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Can we fix it?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.52,0:39:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It'll take time.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.59,0:39:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And by then we'd be out
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.80,0:39:51.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}of international waters.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.39,0:39:55.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Falcon One requesting orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.46,0:39:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}We have a situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.20,0:40:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.66,0:40:03.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The SEAL team failed to neutralize Outis.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.93,0:40:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Somehow the ship's controls were damaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.34,0:40:07.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's headed for Algerian waters
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.68,0:40:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}with our soldiers on boards,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.37,0:40:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}but it'll cause a diplomatic incident
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.94,0:40:13.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}if they stay to finish the job.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.28,0:40:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The navy just made the call to pull the team.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.74,0:40:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All right, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.35,0:40:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The SEALs couldn't do it. We escalate our move.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.25,0:40:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Shouldn't have brought a knife to a gunfight.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.18,0:40:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I will handle from here. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.77,0:40:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.90,0:40:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.40,0:40:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have an ask, one that's imperative.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.34,0:40:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I believe you'll find that our interests are aligned.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.86,0:41:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What are they doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.29,0:41:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}They're leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.29,0:41:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.63,0:41:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.79,0:41:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Oh, God. No, no, no, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:11.32,0:41:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Hey! You're gonna want this.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.07,0:41:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Mike is safe where you can't touch him, and this is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.34,0:41:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}The life, the lies, the mask.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.44,0:41:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}You're gonna tell me everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.18,0:41:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Like who you really are,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.51,0:41:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}what this was, all of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.62,0:42:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It was our life.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.52,0:42:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}It's not over, Sara.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.65,0:42:08.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Not even close.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.42,0:42:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And Mike was never in danger.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.54,0:42:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I love him.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.46,0:42:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}He is my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.12,0:42:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I raised him.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.28,0:42:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}What have you done?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.86,0:42:23.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}No. It's what you've done, Sara.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.77,0:42:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}All of this could've been avoided.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.51,0:42:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Good sleepover?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.81,0:42:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.85,0:42:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Is Mommy coming to pick me up?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.48,0:42:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.39,0:42:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Michael's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.42,0:42:43.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Your Nightingale trip to Greece led me straight to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.03,0:42:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}So... it's all on you, Sara.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:48.60,0:42:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And your plan with Heather didn't work.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.93,0:42:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}Where's my son?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.20,0:42:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}I have him.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:56.54,0:42:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}And whether or not I have to threaten him...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:58.24,0:43:00.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}which I don't want to do...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.18,0:43:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14}is entirely contingent upon you putting the gun down.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(5,15)\p1\fscx116\fscy150\c&H000000&\move(71.2,198.933,32.8,246.933,5,2005)}m m 0 19 l 39 19 l 39 58 l 0 58
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(504,15)\p1\fscx116\fscy150\\c&HFFFFFF&\move(-3.2,290.8,32.4,247.466,5,2005)}m m 0 19 l 39 19 l 39 58 l 0 58
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(1005,15)\p1\fscx116\fscy150\c&H000000&\move(71.2,198.933,32.4,246.4,5,2005)}m 32 27 l 32 27 l 32 29 l 31 29 l 31 28 l 30 28 l 30 29 l 29 29 l 29 30 l 28 30 l 28 31 l 27 31 l 27 32 l 26 32 l 26 33 l 28 33 l 28 32 l 30 32 l 30 33 l 28 33 l 28 34 l 27 34 l 27 36 l 26 36 l 26 37 l 25 37 l 25 36 l 24 36 l 24 33 l 22 33 l 22 32 l 23 32 l 23 31 l 22 31 l 22 30 l 24 30 l 24 31 l 26 31 l 26 30 l 24 30 l 24 28 l 23 28 l 23 29 l 22 29 l 22 30 l 21 30 l 21 31 l 19 31 l 19 32 l 20 32 l 20 33 l 19 33 l 19 32 l 18 32 l 18 33 l 17 33 l 17 32 l 18 32 l 18 31 l 17 31 l 17 30 l 19 30 l 19 29 l 19 29 l 20 29 l 20 30 l 21 30 l 21 29 l 20 29 l 20 28 l 22 28 l 22 27 l 27 27 l 27 28 l 25 28 l 25 29 l 28 29 l 28 25 l 27 25 l 27 26 l 26 26 l 26 25 l 27 25 l 27 24 l 28 24 l 28 23 l 27 23 l 27 22 l 29 22 l 29 27 l 32 27 m 16 29 l 17 29 l 17 28 l 16 28 l 16 29 m 17 26 l 16 26 l 16 25 l 17 25 l 17 26 m 18 29 l 18 27 l 19 27 l 19 26 l 20 26 l 20 25 l 19 25 l 19 26 l 18 26 l 18 25 l 19 25 l 19 24 l 20 24 l 20 22 l 21 22 l 21 21 l 22 21 l 22 24 l 20 24 l 20 25 l 21 25 l 21 27 l 20 27 l 20 28 l 19 28 l 19 29 l 18 29 m 23 26 l 22 26 l 22 25 l 23 25 l 23 26 m 24 26 l 24 24 l 23 24 l 23 21 l 24 21 l 24 22 l 26 22 l 26 24 l 25 24 l 25 26 m 0 28 l 0 30 l 1 30 l 1 29 l 2 29 l 2 30 l 3 30 l 3 33 l 2 33 l 2 34 l 1 34 l 1 33 l 0 33 l 0 34 l 1 34 l 1 35 l 2 35 l 2 37 l 1 37 l 1 36 l 0 36 l 0 38 l 2 38 l 2 39 l 5 39 l 5 40 l 7 40 l 7 39 l 6 39 l 6 38 l 8 38 l 8 37 l 9 37 l 9 36 l 10 36 l 10 37 l 11 37 l 11 36 l 10 36 l 10 34 l 9 34 l 9 36 l 8 36 l 8 34 l 9 34 l 9 33 l 6 33 l 6 32 l 5 32 l 5 31 l 6 31 l 6 32 l 8 32 l 8 31 l 6 31 l 6 30 l 8 30 l 8 28 l 7 28 l 7 29 l 6 29 l 6 30 l 4 30 l 4 28 l 5 28 l 5 29 l 6 29 l 6 28 l 7 28 l 7 27 l 6 27 l 6 28 l 5 28 l 5 27 l 2 27 l 2 28 l 3 28 l 3 29 l 2 29 l 2 28 l 1 28 m 0 31 l 2 31 l 2 32 l 0 32 m 9 31 l 10 31 l 10 32 l 9 32 l 9 31 m 21 32 l 22 32 l 22 31 l 21 31 l 21 32 m 37 27 l 34 27 l 34 28 l 33 28 l 33 29 l 32 29 l 32 30 l 31 30 l 31 29 l 30 29 l 30 32 l 31 32 l 31 33 l 30 33 l 30 34 l 29 34 l 29 36 l 28 36 l 28 37 l 26 37 l 26 40 l 25 40 l 25 41 l 24 41 l 24 39 l 23 39 l 23 41 l 24 41 l 24 43 l 22 43 l 22 42 l 19 42 l 19 43 l 20 43 l 20 44 l 21 44 l 21 45 l 19 45 l 19 46 l 22 46 l 22 44 l 25 44 l 25 41 l 26 41 l 26 44 l 27 44 l 27 42 l 28 42 l 28 44 l 30 44 l 30 45 l 32 45 l 32 46 l 33 46 l 33 45 l 34 45 l 34 44 l 35 44 l 35 43 l 33 43 l 33 45 l 32 45 l 32 44 l 32 42 l 31 42 l 31 43 l 30 43 l 30 42 l 29 42 l 29 41 l 26 41 l 26 40 l 27 40 l 27 38 l 28 38 l 28 39 l 29 39 l 29 41 l 30 41 l 30 42 l 31 42 l 31 41 l 32 41 l 32 40 l 34 40 l 34 41 l 34 42 l 36 42 l 36 44 l 37 44 l 37 43 l 37 40 l 36 40 l 36 41 l 35 41 l 35 39 l 36 39 l 36 38 l 37 38 l 37 37 l 35 37 l 35 35 l 34 35 l 34 36 l 33 36 l 33 37 l 35 37 l 35 39 l 33 39 l 33 37 l 32 37 l 32 38 l 30 38 l 30 39 l 29 39 l 29 38 l 28 38 l 28 37 l 30 37 l 30 36 l 31 36 l 31 37 l 32 37 l 32 36 l 33 36 l 33 34 l 34 34 l 34 33 l 35 33 l 35 34 l 36 34 l 36 35 l 37 35 l 37 33 l 35 33 l 35 31 l 32 31 l 32 30 l 33 30 l 33 29 l 35 29 l 35 28 l 37 28 l 37 27 m 33 32 l 33 33 l 32 33 l 32 32 m 31 34 l 32 34 l 32 35 l 31 35 m 25 35 l 26 35 l 26 34 l 25 34 m 36 29 l 36 29 l 37 29 l 37 30 l 36 30 m 36 31 l 37 31 l 37 32 l 36 32 m 14 36 l 14 34 l 13 34 l 13 35 l 12 35 l 12 38 l 13 38 l 13 36 m 4 38 l 4 37 l 3 37 l 3 38 l 2 38 l 2 37 l 3 37 l 3 33 l 5 33 l 5 34 l 4 34 l 4 35 l 6 35 l 6 34 l 7 34 l 7 35 l 6 35 l 6 36 l 7 36 l 7 37 l 6 37 l 6 38 l 4 38 m 4 36 l 5 36 l 5 37 l 4 37 m 37 46 l 37 45 l 36 45 l 36 44 l 35 44 l 35 45 l 34 45 l 34 46 l 35 46 l 35 47 l 34 47 l 34 48 l 35 48 l 35 51 l 34 51 l 34 53 l 33 53 l 33 55 l 31 55 l 31 54 l 32 54 l 32 53 l 33 53 l 33 50 l 34 50 l 34 49 l 33 49 l 33 47 l 29 47 l 29 46 l 28 46 l 28 47 l 27 47 l 27 46 l 28 46 l 28 45 l 26 45 l 26 47 l 25 47 l 25 48 l 24 48 l 24 46 l 25 46 l 25 45 l 23 45 l 23 47 l 21 47 l 21 48 l 20 48 l 20 47 l 19 47 l 19 50 l 21 50 l 21 53 l 19 53 l 19 54 l 21 54 l 21 56 l 23 56 l 23 55 l 22 55 l 22 54 l 23 54 l 23 53 l 22 53 l 22 52 l 24 52 l 24 53 l 25 53 l 25 52 l 26 52 l 26 51 l 25 51 l 25 50 l 24 50 l 24 51 l 22 51 l 22 50 l 23 50 l 23 49 l 26 49 l 26 48 l 28 48 l 28 49 l 28 49 l 26 49 l 26 51 l 27 51 l 27 50 l 28 50 l 28 51 l 27 51 l 27 52 l 28 52 l 28 54 l 27 54 l 27 53 l 26 53 l 26 56 l 28 56 l 28 55 l 29 55 l 29 52 l 30 52 l 30 53 l 31 53 l 31 52 l 32 52 l 32 53 l 31 53 l 31 54 l 30 54 l 30 55 l 29 55 l 29 56 l 37 56 l 37 53 l 36 53 l 36 55 l 34 55 l 34 54 l 35 54 l 35 51 l 37 51 l 37 49 l 36 49 l 36 46 m 29 48 l 32 48 l 32 51 l 29 51 m 30 49 l 31 49 l 31 50 l 30 50 m 13 50 l 15 50 l 15 47 l 16 47 l 16 46 l 17 46 l 17 45 l 18 45 l 18 43 l 17 43 l 17 42 l 14 42 l 14 43 l 16 43 l 16 46 l 15 46 l 15 44 l 14 44 l 14 43 l 13 43 l 13 45 l 11 45 l 11 44 l 12 44 l 12 43 l 9 43 l 9 45 l 8 45 l 8 43 l 6 43 l 6 42 l 10 42 l 10 40 l 11 40 l 11 42 l 13 42 l 13 41 l 14 41 l 14 40 l 13 40 l 13 41 l 12 41 l 12 40 l 11 40 l 11 38 l 9 38 l 9 39 l 8 39 l 8 41 l 5 41 l 5 42 l 3 42 l 3 41 l 0 41 l 0 43 l 1 43 l 1 42 l 2 42 l 2 44 l 0 44 l 0 48 l 1 48 l 1 45 l 2 45 l 2 47 l 3 47 l 3 45 l 2 45 l 2 44 l 3 44 l 3 43 l 4 43 l 4 48 l 5 48 l 5 47 l 6 47 l 6 46 l 7 46 l 7 45 l 6 45 l 6 44 l 5 44 l 5 43 l 6 43 l 6 44 l 7 44 l 7 45 l 8 45 l 8 47 l 6 47 l 6 48 l 8 48 l 8 49 l 9 49 l 9 46 l 10 46 l 10 45 l 11 45 l 11 46 l 10 46 l 10 47 l 11 47 l 11 48 l 10 48 l 10 49 l 11 49 l 11 48 l 14 48 l 14 49 l 13 49 m 13 47 l 12 47 l 12 46 l 13 46 m 15 56 l 11 56 l 11 55 l 9 55 l 9 54 l 8 54 l 8 51 l 9 51 l 9 53 l 10 53 l 10 50 l 11 50 l 11 54 l 12 54 l 12 52 l 13 52 l 13 51 l 14 51 l 14 52 l 13 52 l 13 54 l 12 54 l 12 55 l 15 55 l 15 55 m 15 54 l 15 53 l 17 53 l 17 54 l 18 54 l 18 56 l 16 56 l 16 54 m 17 48 l 18 48 l 18 50 l 16 50 l 16 49 l 17 49 m 17 51 l 18 51 l 18 52 l 17 52 m 19 51 l 20 51 l 20 52 l 19 52 m 19 55 l 20 55 l 20 56 l 19 56 m 0 39 l 1 39 l 1 40 l 0 40 m 0 49 l 7 49 l 7 56 l 0 56 l 0 56 m 1 50 l 1 55 l 1 55 l 6 55 l 6 50 m 2 51 l 5 51 l 5 54 l 2 54 m 30 19 l 30 26 l 37 26 l 37 19 m 31 20 l 36 20 l 36 25 l 31 25 m 32 21 l 32 24 l 35 24 l 35 21 m 0 19 l 7 19 l 7 26 l 0 26 m 1 20 l 1 25 l 6 25 l 6 20 m 2 21 l 2 24 l 5 24 l 5 21 m 8 19 l 8 22 l 11 22 l 11 23 l 10 23 l 10 24 l 8 24 l 8 28 l 10 28 l 10 29 l 12 29 l 12 33 l 10 33 l 10 34 l 11 34 l 11 35 l 12 35 l 12 34 l 13 34 l 13 33 l 15 33 l 15 32 l 16 32 l 16 30 l 15 30 l 15 31 l 14 31 l 14 30 l 15 30 l 15 29 l 14 29 l 14 28 l 13 28 l 13 24 l 15 24 l 15 25 l 14 25 l 14 27 l 15 27 l 15 28 l 16 28 l 16 26 l 15 26 l 15 25 l 16 25 l 16 24 l 17 24 l 17 25 l 18 25 l 18 23 l 19 23 l 19 21 l 21 21 l 21 20 l 23 20 l 23 19 l 21 19 l 21 20 l 19 20 l 19 19 l 18 19 l 18 21 l 17 21 l 17 23 l 15 23 l 15 22 l 16 22 l 16 21 l 17 21 l 17 20 l 16 20 l 16 21 l 15 21 l 15 20 l 16 20 l 16 19 l 14 19 l 14 21 l 15 21 l 15 22 l 14 22 l 14 21 l 13 21 l 13 22 l 12 22 l 12 20 l 13 20 l 13 19 l 11 19 l 11 20 l 9 20 l 9 19 m 9 27 l 9 25 l 10 25 l 10 24 l 11 24 l 11 23 l 12 23 l 12 28 l 11 28 l 11 27 m 10 26 l 10 25 l 11 25 l 11 26 m 25 19 l 25 20 l 26 20 l 26 19 m 28 19 l 29 19 l 29 21 l 27 21 l 27 20 l 28 20
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\c&H000000&\4c&H000000&\4a&HFF&\3c&H000000&\3a&HFF&\fscx16\fscy26\move(71.2,198.933,32.443,248.194,5,2005)}m 56 35 l 43 41 l 52 41 l 52 39 l 56 39 m 73 28 l 77 41 l 82 41 m 69 21 l 61 21 l 64 23 l 64 39 l 63 41 l 70 41 l 65 28 l 67 23 l 71 23 m 25 28 l 17 41 l 33 41 m 31 21 l 52 21 l 42 25 l 42 29 l 53 24 l 55 26 l 42 32 l 42 35 l 56 29 l 56 31 l 42 37 l 41 39 m 29 9 l 55 9 l 55 11 l 41 11 l 41 17 l 51 17 l 51 14 l 65 14 l 68 18 l 29 18 m 20 11 l 16 18 l 20 18 m 14 21 l 19 21 l 8 39 l 7 39 l 7 41 l 1 41
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.82,0:43:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\pos(381.427,-4.581)\fad(484,714)\b0}
